OK... Here we go. Focus.
81961, !റ്9 ന്ധില്്ല. ൦ഠ1വട.
Speed. lam speed.
(രിച്ന. ഷവ ലി ക്ല്ധ്ന.
One winner, 42 losers.
൭൦0190 0 ന൦00൭, ബ്വാബ്വാധിഥ യയ.
l eat losers for breakfast.
എവ നലിത്നന്ന്വ൭ു വല ഥി യ്യാ.
Breakfast.
ല്ഖ്വാന.
Wait, maybe I should have had breakfast.
൧ിവാദ്ഡ' ടല്ഘ്വാന ഠ്ഥ്വ.
A little breck-y could be good for me. No, no, no, stay focused. Speed.
ദ്രിദ്ധ ടഖ്്വാന ഠ്ധ്വ സ്വ വട. 1ഠിപിഷരിഖബ്ഠഡട. (രല.
I'm faster than fast. Quicker than quick.
൧യലാപ്ാഖ്ടട ദ നട. ലോ ഠ്ലി ലോ.
lam lightning!
ചവ ഠിടില്വ്ിട!
Hey, Lightning! You ready?
൦, ഠി ദ്ധ ഠ്ലി ട൦ഠി9?
Oh, yeah. Lightning's ready.
൨൧ ഠവല
Get your antenna balls here!
8ധ 0ഠ19 ൩ഠ്൯മര്ധഭ ടബ്‌!
Go, Lightnin’!
ഷുഡ്‌ ടല്യഷ്ാ!
You got that right, slick.
ഴിണഘാലാദ്ധി ഒ ത്ധി
Welcome back to the Dinoco 400.
ലന ഠ്ട്ണ്ു !ഭ ൧0൦ 400.
I'm Bob Cutlass, here with my good friend, Darrell Cartrip.
ചവ 8ംാ ഥിടടട ഠി ട്ബ്വാണഭാനട ത്ന 0ലിമിവ ഥി ഠദണ്0..
We're midway through what may be an historic day for racing.
.൧൭ഠ്9 ഗ്‌ ൧ല്നാഒെ 7 ലല
Bob, my oil pressure's through the roof.
7ലക്ഥഥ നഖ ൮ ദ്ദ ടഒ്യാല്‌ധാഗ്ന്ഥാഥന്റ്‌
If this gets more exciting, they're gonna have to tow me outta the booth!
കഥ 'ലഥഥ ഖഡ്൮ഒ റ്ഥ്‌ ൨, (ക്ട! ഖഗ ഖ്‌
Right you are, Darrell.
ഥ്ല്ഥ്‌ (ക്൭ ൭൧.
Three cars are tied for the season points lead,
7499 ഖഭ്ട നലന്ഥഥഗഷ്‌ നദ ൭ ടഖനഒ..
heading into the final race of the season.
..ഥണറ്റഗ്വാഥറെ നട 75൩ ൧൨.
And the winner of this race will win the season title and the Piston Cup.
൧ നെറ ാല്ധ്്ഥാണെ ൨ ഒക
Does The King, Strip Weathers,
൧റ്൭ക് ശെ 14ഒ9൭0ല്‌ട
have one more victory in him before retirement?
20൭0 ഗനലണലമഥറ്റ്‌ ടദ്ധ ഒ ാല്ധ്്ഥാണ ട്ലോല്ഥന ഗാല?
He's been Dinoco's golden boy for years!
൧൭ 20൧9 ലനടെ 77000൧ ഗല്ലാഥ 'ഒന ലു!
Can he win them one last Piston Cup?
എഴഒന്വാഥ വട നനെ ൧൭'9 ൧5൧ ഒഗ്ഗ7 ശ്ഗണറ്റ്‌
And, as always, in the second place spot we find Chick Hicks.
ഥു ടല്വാലന്‌ ൧ഒ.59, വ്‌ ലനാ! (൭൧൭ :൭(൭0 ൨04൮ഥല൪..
He's been chasing that tailfin his entire career.
൧൭ (൭൭7 4ലന്വാട! ല്ല ട്ല്ഗ്ഥ ക്ഗ്ലനു൭.
Chick thought this was his year, Bob.
ഗ്വവകറ്ര ഖഗ ൧൨ ന്ദ ഒക്ഥ സന ലമററ്റ.
His chance to finally emerge from The King's shadow.
൧ല്ധമഥറ്റുഭ ശല റ്൭7്‌ ഗദൃഭ്ഥറുറ ൧൧.
But the last thing he expected was...
൧ ലശലഴ ന്ദ ദറ്ഭ (൭(൭൨ ..ഗ്ഒി7ഥേഥടവ്‌
..Lightning McQueen!
൨൧ ഠവല
You know, I don't think anybody expected this.
൧൧൧൫5൭ 4ഒ ഒറ ട4ഒ൧൭ )൭ 50൦൪൭.
The rookie sensation came into the season unknown.
൧ല്ഗ്ലാദക്ഗ ൧ല്ഒനട റ്ഥ്ഥ 1ഒ4 ൭4൭ (൭ഥ൭! ന്൭
But everyone knows him now.
ഒ്ല7 ടലഭ്വമഥറ്റ ഖന 7 (൭൧൨൭..
Will he be the first rookie to win a Piston Cup and land Dinoco?
൧൧൭൫൭ വ്ഒ ഒ൫൧ ൭൨൪ ൧ല(൧൩൧൭ ൧൨ ൧ല൭നട )൭ നറെഒററ്റ 09(൭ ൧5(00
The legend, the runner-up, and the rookie!
൧ലഗ്ന൧ഒ [ഒറ്റലറ്ട, ൧ലനലമററ്റ (൭ഠ്൭ റ്൭റ ാല്൧൩൧൭ ൧൭7൧
Three cars, one champion!
7499 ഖഴ്ട റ്റ ദ്ധ!
No, you don't.
1ലിപ്മി൦ഠില്‍ ൦൦!
What a ride!
- ദ്ധ ലാട! - ലിധസ്ാ ലാണ്‌
Go get 'em, McQueen! Go get 'em!
ലറ്റി ഠിദ്വദ്ധിദ്ഥ സ്റ്പ്ഗിറ്വേടബ്‌
I love you, Lightning!
ചവ ഗ്ടിഖ്ലയ്ധ, ധി!
Dinoco is all mine.
ലയ ൧൯൦൦ ന॥॥ലിവ.
Trouble, turn three!
ഗാട, ടലില്ര്വിഷിറും!
- Get through that, McQueen. - A huge crash behind the leaders!
- ധാമ ധ്ധ ല്ല, [ഗിീറ്ധേലണ - (നിണ ഠിവാലല്ഖ്യാ ലധ്സാ ധ്ണട
Wait a second, Darrell. McQueen is in the wreckage.
പുലി ല്ല, ൧൦॥! ഴിഗ്ധ൦ബാല്മഠട ഠ। ട്വ.
There's no way the rookie can make it through!
7ഒലനഥനഗ ഥല്ഗ്ാട ഗാഡ വ്‌ 20൭൨ !ലാഒട റ്റ്ഗ ടല
Not in one piece, that is.
ല്ല 0ിദ്വിഘല്ബുഒ.
Lightning!
[]:
Look at that! McQueen made it through!
[ഗിഠ്ധ൦൦ ട൦൭ണ3 നലിലാദട്സഭ!
Man, a spectacular move by Lightning McQueen!
ദരിയ ലാമ ൦൦൩ [ഗിറ്വേടബ്‌
Yeah! Ka-chow!
൭ ലീലാ!
McQueen! McQueen! McQueen!
[ഴിഗ്ധ൦വ്‌ [ഴ്വ [ഗീഠ്ധട്‌
While everyone else heads into the pits, McQueen stays out to take the lead!
ലട ടലന്ധട ഭലാ! 2ിലാന്പാലിയന, [ഗിഠ്ധ൦൦0 നദ ൫ മഠ്ല്രാദ്ബ്‌
Don't take me out, coach. I can still race!
പത്സിര്ധലിത്ഥ ലവ, ടവ നടട്വാഠില്വാലിധസാല്‍!
What do you think? A thing of beauty.
ദാറുല്‌? ടദ്ധിശഷ്ന്ന്മ്മ്.
- McQueen made it through! - What?
[ഗിഠ്ധ൦ബാല]ദയഭ ലാമട!
He's not pitting!
൧19 1ടലാണല്സ്‌!
You gotta get me out there! Let's go! Get me back out there!
ലിക ടവ ക്ല ടന്ധിട! കൃഡ്വ്‌
McQueen's not going into the pits!
[ഗിഠ്ധ൦൦ബല്ധാണണി ധിവാണ്ഡാലിയ്ല്‍്‌
The rookie just fired his crew chief. That's the third one this season!
൧1 ലാബ ട്വ 0൦0൭ ര്ധാന്ദധ, ഴു ക്വാ സ്പട്ന ബ്‌!
- He says he likes working alone. - Go, go, go!
രബ ഠി ടധിയ്വാലഷ്ട ടലി.
Looks like Chick got caught up in the pits.
ഉ വഗടടംയാഡ്‌ ഠി ന്ദ ലാസ്ബാലിത്വ.
Yeah, after a stop like that, he's got a lot of ground to make up.
൧19 ബട ഘ്ല ടണ്ഡിദ.
Get ready, boys, we're coming to the restart!
8ലടലഠി, 09 ടിയ സ്ധിഒ.
Come on, come on, come on!
ലോട്‌ ലോബ്‌
We need tires now! Come on, let's go!
ദരി വാലിധിക്ന മവ ടലഷ്ഥണ്!
- No, no, no, no! No tires, just gas! - What?
1ഠിപ്ഠിറ പന ധിഖ് മര, ന്നാ ന്ദ്‌
You need tires, you idiot!
൧൭൦! (ദ്ധ ലാല്ധിത്ന ഒ, ഠി!
Looks like it's all gas-and-go's for McQueen today.
[ഗിഠ്ധ൦൦ന൫ബ൫൭ ടി സ്സ ജഘി ബ്‌.
That's right. No tires again.
ഴിണഘാാദ്ധി. ലയ! 1 ലിഡിയ വ.
That's a short-term gain, long-term loss, but it's sure workin’ for him.
ലല്ധസമം വ ഭ്ധ്ധാബഘായ ലാല ൦ ഭഡാ!ബുഘാാബ്ുനണ്യ
He obviously knows somethin’ we don't know.
പിലദട ടലയ॥ ഠി 1൨ ടല്ധ്ധവ ന്മ ല്ഗ്സ.
This is it, Darrell.
ല്വട്പ്രവ്പ ചല
One lap to go and Lightning McQueen has a huge lead.
ദ്ധ ധ്യ! ിബഗി്ധ൦൦ നലഠ്ല്ഡിധി [ദ്ധ ഠ1 9൦0൭0.
He's got it in the bag. Call in the dogs and put out the fire!
൧19 9510 സ്വ നന്മ. ധാധ്‌ നബുനറമ്ല്‍്‌
We're gonna crown us a new champion!
ഗ്മ ൭൦൭ നദ്വത്ലിയ്ബ്്മാട്സ്‌
Checkered flag, here I come!
ല്ല ഹന്മനട്‌, ബി മവ ഠ്ദ്ബാ!
Oh, no! McQueen has blown a tire!
ദൃദ്വ ഗിവ്‌
And with only one turn to go! Can he make it?
ഉഹു ടബ്ബ വട്ാ്ബിാ!! ൧ ഠി മിഖ്ബാലുദ്യര?
McQueen's blown a tire!
1ദൃദ്വഗീഠ്ധ൦൦റ ദ്വ! !
Go, go, go!
ലലറ്റി, ലയി, യ
He's lost another tire!
ദ്ധ ൮ ഒ ദ ൧ഠഠദ്വ്‌
- King and Chick are coming up fast! - They're entering turn three!
ഗ്ര ൦ ്ബ്ഗനമ്ടമ ്നണോദ്ബാദ്മട! -[ഗീലനാട്ധിറി ടലല്ര ഭൂമ!
Come on.
ഷഡി
I don't believe what I'm watching, Bob!
൧൮ മലാല ലാ ൮൭ മിവ ന്റ്‌
Lightning McQueen is 100 feet from his Piston Cup!
ഴിഗ്ധ൦ബാല്ദഠ്ദ ടല്ദ്ധട നല്ല ഠ്‌ ലം[ദ ലിട്ബ്‌
The King and Chick rounding turn four.
ഗ്ന ൦ ബല്‍ നലാ്പാ॥ ടടില്‍ലര൩ിഭല്പാദ്‌.
Down the stretch they come! And it's, and it's...
[ഗി ഠ്ദ്ാ ൪ ലിടബാണ്ടമ്‌ ൧0 19..
- It's too close to call! Too close! - [don't believe it!
- 9 1ലിദ്ധ ടയ ഥി ലാലിയ - ധിയഖ നല്ലാ സമയി!
- The most spectacular, amazing... - [don't believe it!
രട്ധ്മ്ന്൭ 02100 നട്ബിറുധാത്ന, ഘാ...
.. unequivocally, unbelievable ending in the history of the world!
- 0 ടിയ ഠ്0ാലമ്യി -൧ിവ നടില്ല!
- And we don't know who won! - Look at that!
ഉമ ലസ ടിലാര്‍ നടണ്മ്യ!
Hey, no cameras! Get outta here!
ദ്ദ നല! ൧! ഠ്ലി ട്ബ്‌!
We're here in Victory Lane, awaiting the results.
കത ദെ സ ലഥറ്റുഥ (ഭ്വാശ്ധടഒഥ ഖ്‌.
McQueen, that was a risky move, not taking tires.
൧709, (൭൧ ൧7 ഗ്ര ഒഗനഹധ്രഗ ഒര
Tell me about it!
എദ്ഒണെററ ഒധ 1൭0൧.
Are you sorry you didn't have a crew chief out there?
74൭൨൮൭5൭! (൭൧ ഒ ൭9 (ഥാ ഗഥാ7
Oh, Kori. There's a lot more to racing than just winning.
൧്ല്ഗ്ാട വ ാഥത്ഥ ശ്ലനഗെെറ്റ 590൭൫.
! mean, taking the race by a full lap... Where's the entertainment in that?
എഴലകറ്റ ടേ ാഥഗേററെ 0൧, ഒരാ) നലലഡ്ുകത്ഥ?
! wanted to give folks a little sizzle.
൧൧ഥ൭ഥണ്‌ ഗ്ഗ നഗുകഷ്‌ധറധശ്കഥ.
- Sizzle? - Am I sorry I don't have a crew chief?
൧൧ ന)൭൭5൭! 49 ഒറ്ട (കഥ (ഗഗെ7
No, I'm not. ‘Cause I'm a one-man show.
7൨% ഒധാാലര്ധുട ഹേന
What? Oh, yeah, right.
൧൧൭7 0൧൭, ഥല്‌.
That was a confident Lightning McQueen.
ഗഗ ഗ്ഒ77ഥുഥറ ത വാലഥഥ ;(ഭൃഷ്ധഗ്നെ.
Live from Victory Lane, I'm Kori Turbowitz.
[ടന ൭ ഗ്ഗ ൨൦൭൭. ചവ ധി ധനാഠ്മ.
Get outta the shot.
രല!
Yo, Chuck, what are you doing? You're blockin' the camera!
ഡംപത്ഖ നലം ൭ണല്൭!
- Everyone wants to see the bolt. - What?
ലന്ധട നു നമി 109 റിങ്ലഖ.
- Now, back away. - That's it! Come on, guys.
ടം
- Whoa, team! Where are you going? - We quit, Mr. One-Man Show!
- റ്ധിഡ്വ! ഗീ ്൨ ന്ദിലാല്യ്്‌? - ദ്ര ലല്ലു, 2൨. ദ്വ ട്‌!
Oh, OK, leave. Fine.
8109, ൧0൭. 1ഒഗ്വാദ
How will l ever find anyone else who knows how to fill me up with gas?
ഗീാഠഠണാന ടവ ന്ഥി ഗു ധ്ലട। സ്സ
- Adios, Chuck! - And my name is not Chuck!
- ൭ലണമ്ന്ന്യാല്‍, ല്ഡംറ പണട മിവ ാധിത്ഥ ഡം
Oh, whatever.
ടിയ ന്ധ
Hey, Lightning! Yo! McQueen!
ല്‍, [ഠി
Seriously, that was some pretty darn nice racin' out there.
ലാട ഹാലി ഠി ട്ട 19൦.
- By me! - Oh, yeah.
ഠി ലവ്‌
- Zinger! - Welcome to the Chick era, baby!
ലണ്ട്‌ ഠ്യ ഭ ഒ ബിലാ
The Piston Cup... It's mine, dude. It's mine.
ല്ലം 0500 ന॥॥ലിവ.
Hey, fellas, how do you think I'd look in Dinoco blue? Dinoco blue!
ദ്ധ ഒട നാഠമ്നമ സ്വാ മിഡാഡഘന്ന ബസ ഥിനാഠോ?
In your dreams, Thunder.
ദ്ബന്വി ടലി സ്ഥല.
Yeah, right. Thunder? What's he talkin’ about, "Thunder"?
൧൧൭ നലിത്ധാ ഠിം, സ്ഥ?
You know, ‘cause thunder always comes after lightning.
ലാലാ 2 ടല്ല്ധ ക്നാ ടല്ല്ാദട 109.
- Who knew about the thunder thing? - l didn't.
൧ ട്ലി ടില്ാഠ ട്ഡദയി്വന്മഥു ഴി?
- Give us the bolt! - That's right.
1 ധബ്ധിറമ്ല്ഖ്ി ബ്ട ഴി!
- Show me the bolt, McQueen! - That's it!
ലാക്‌! ലാട!
That was one close finish. You sure made Dinoco proud.
ധഭട്ധഠ്ല്മ്സഭ ടബണിഘ്പ!. ദ്ധാധ ഥന 003.
Thank you, King.
ലന ഒട, ഗ്ന
Well, Tex, you've been good to me all these years.
1പെര്ധലാടിലാടഠ്ട ടവ ടലണട 1൩.
It's the least I could do.
ബി ടല ഠ്വ ടിവിത്വ.
Whatever happens, you're a winner to me, you old daddy rabbit.
൧൧൪ ലിവ, 11:11 :1511:10
Thanks, dear. Wouldn't be nothing without you.
ലന മടി, ടന. കില്ല ലിവ ബാ ത്ധ.
- I'm Mia. - I'm Tia.
-൧ിവ ഗി. -൧ിവ 1019.
We're, like, your biggest fans! Ka-chow!
ദരി വാന്‌ ടലി ത്വ.
I love being me.
൧൮ ട്ധിയടഠി ഠ്ഥിവ.
- OK, girls, that's it. - We love you, Lightning!
ഡ്ധിഡ്വ
Hey, buddy. You're one gutsy racer.
ദ്ധ, ന്വ ഥല്ധമ്പാുര്‍ാന്്ബി
Oh, hey, Mr. The King.
൭൨, ലി ബ്നു.
You got more talent in one lug nut
ദ്ധ ടാാദ്ലാണലിയ!
than a lot of cars has got in their whole body.
ലാ ബ്രാം ഘട ൩.
- Really? Oh, that... - But you're stupid.
ര? ൭൨.. - ലല ദ്ധാഠഠ൦1൨
- Excuse me? - This ain't a one-man deal, kid.
-൧്യാടിന്ധ യ്മ? - ബാധിത ടധിത്ന ട്ടി.
You need to wise up and get a good crew chief and a good team.
ദ്ധ നട്ട്‌ ടല ൦ ദോ ഭ്ധാ ന ്ഖ്ബാടട്ധിയ്സുരാലിം
You ain't gonna win unless you got good folks behind you,
ദ്ധ ലിലി നങ്ങ നലലത ലാല]
and you let them do their job, like they should.
ഴു 0ലിഗനബ്ബുലിമ്ബ്ത്ഥ വാട ന്നി.
- Like I tell the boys at the shop... - Agood team.
പി
If you figure that out you just gonna be OK.
ള॥ടയ്ധ റ ടലഠില, വ ദിഖ്ബിലാവ്വാദിം
Oh, yeah, that... That is spectacular advice.
നടി നമ്ര ലാ.
Thank you, Mr. The King.
ലന ഒട, £പഗ്ണു.
Ladies and gentlemen,
ദ്ധ-ഡണണ ക ല്ധാധണ,
for the first time in Piston Cup history...
ലനാ തിസ ിന ടല ലം ൧ടഠ൩..
A rookie has won the Piston Cup.
൭൦9 ലാല്ധസ്പാാബ് 1ലല നണഠനന്മന! ലം[ദ ൧൭൧൩.
Yes!
1 1)
..we have a three-way tie.
09 09 19 വല ൮൬൭ ടലി.
Hey, McQueen, that must be really embarrassing.
വ നദ നണദ്ധിത്നസു
But I wouldn't worry about it. Because I didn't do it!
ല്ല മവ മിഗലിത്ഥ റ്ടദ്ധ ന്ഥ. ലാലാ മിവ ലിധില്വിയ്സു!
Piston Cup officials have determined that a tiebreaker race
ഥ്ിനല്ധാലിയാട 50 നന്ധ്വടിത്ന ലയെ ഹലിധ്സാബാലലസ്ധദ
between the three leaders will be held in California in one week.
ഗലിധ്ധാബാലലസ്ധറ ന്മ ന്ധിലിത്ന ഠി ഠി ബി ടബ്ബ സ്ാധ 1.
Well, thank you! Thanks to all of you out there! Thank you!
ലന മടി! ലന മടി ഭ്വാദഠ്ദ ടന്ധട ഠി ധല ടട!
Hey, rook, first one to California gets Dinoco all to himself.
ണാ ന്ന ഭ ഗണി, 90 ട്ടറി ൦൦ ഥന
No, not me! No, you rock, and you know that!
ധി മിവ! 1ഠിപിത്ധ നനന ലാട ്ബിത്ധ ണ്ട!
Oh, yeah!
ഠപ്൮ു൪
"First one to California gets Dinoco all to himself."
“രുന്ന ടണ്ഡാ! ഠലഗ്ബഃ ത്ന 90 ്ടഹാറ്ദ ൦൦ ഥന”
Oh, we'll see who gets there first, Chick.
ന്മ 1൭൧0 ട്രാ ടന്വാലി ഠ്്ധ, ഠ്വ.
- Hey, kid! Congrats on the tie. - [don't want to talk about it.
- ഠി ല്ല 0 ടി -൧ിവ 1ട1ഗന്മ്വാന്ലിത്വാ നഘുഠ്മ്സുഒ.
- l parked it at your sponsor's tent. - What?
പിഗിഖ്ന 1ടില മിവ? -ടലാല്ല്വനണല ഒ്ഥില്്ത്ധ.
Gotta make your personal appearance.
ദ്ധ നട്ട്‌ ൨ ലാണ്ടന്ധ!ടന ഹബാദഠി
No. No! No, no, no, no!
1ഠിപ്ഥിപ്ഠിറ
Yes, yes, yes! Lightning McQueen here.
ക്ക! ൧൧ ഗോ.
And Il use Rust-eze Medicated Bumper Ointment, new rear end formula!
ഥു ഖഗ റഗലര്ഥ ി7വ൮൭ഥലഥട്‌ ൧5൭ ൧0ന്‌ ൧൭7൧
Nothing soothes a rusty bumper like Rust-eze.
74ഒറ്ട )൬ നലറ്റെട'ക്റ 504 ൧൧519൭2൭.
Wow! Look at that shine!
ഥാ 7൭ ഗെ ഗ്ഥ്‌
Use Rust-eze and you too can look like me!
ഗേ ഥമ റ്റ (ഥഗ൮൭9 ഒര്ഥ ഗ7്‌ഒന്വാല ക്രാ ൭ധ്‌
I met this car from Swampscott.
എഡ്ൃധ്വാ ഘട ഠി ധേല്വാടഠ്‌.
He was so rusty he didn't even cast a shadow.
19 നദ്ധാലിത്ധവാോ 151 നല്ന്യാലിബാദത്ാപാഖത്ാ ൧൧൩.
You could see his dirty undercarriage.
!ദ്ധാഠില്‍ നന്വാ% ലിനാ വയ യം.
I hate rusty cars. This is not good for my image.
ഡാലി ഭ൭്വാലിത്വ്‌. ബ ധാം॥ഗധിണല്‍ ൮.
They did give you your big break. Besides, it's in your contract.
[ഗി0ിലാലി ത്ധവാല്ധമ്നാ ടട. ഉ ഒഠ9 ഠിന്രന്ത്ല്ലത്ധ.
Oh, will you stop, please? Just go get hooked up.
8ഠില്നത്ധ നസ്പിത്ഥ? ലലറ്ി ട്പാധന്യ ഭ തടില ലിവ.
- Winter is a grand old time. - Of this there are no ifs or buts.
[ള്‍്ധടിന ടല്ധിധമണട നലിയ. - ിദഠിദിയ ദ്ദ്ധ ഖല്വാ.
But remember, all that salt and grime...
ലന ടന്ധ പണ ഠ്ബി്ര്തം്
Can rust your bolts and freeze your...
8ഠില വ ടിസ ദ്ധി ഠ്കനഥല്‍ഡിത്ന..
Hey, look! There he is!
ധ്യാഥറ ഠി!
Our almost champ!
സ്ഥല നട!
Get your rear end in here, kid.
[ഗി ഭ ട്വ.
Lightning McQueen, you are wicked fast!
ദ്ധ മണ ലാദ്മട!
- That race was a pisser! - You were booking!
- ലിധസ്ധാണ ബ ടബ്‌ നന്ട്റുധാത്ല്‍്‌ -ര്ര്ധ ടണ്‌ ന്ടട!
- Give me a little room. - You're my hero!
- 8ലിത്ന മിവ ടലി ബാ -ര്ര്ധ ഗ്‌ ടിവി!
Yes, I know.
൮൭, ലിധല്ഡ.
"Fred." Fred, thank you.
..൧൭9.
He knows my name. He knows my name!
൧19 15ധ നന ലിഡ്‌
Looking good, Freddie!
ദ്ധ നലന്വാടറവഘാട്‌, €ഭാഠില്‍
Thanks to you, Lightning, we had a banner year!
ലന ഒടി ൧9 ത്വ, ടന ബനാ!
We might clear enough to buy you some headlights.
ഗ്ധന്ിന്൩ ഡിഡ്വാ ഥിലാല॥[ത്ലത്ധ സ്വ നന.
You saying he doesn't have headlights?
൧19 1951 ഠി സ്വധാ?
That's what I'm telling ya. They're stickers!
1, ണ്ട ാലലയ്‌
Well, you know, racecars don't need headlights,
ല്യം മലാലിധിത്ല സ്ഥ ന്നാ
because the track is always lit.
ടലാദ്ധ ധാ ടനണിടടദ ജല.
Yeah, well, so is my brother, but he still needs headlights.
൧ ലിവ്്ഥവാട്ഖ, ദ്വ നടടിവ്വാലിധിത്നി വ്വ 00.
Ladies and gentlemen, Lightning McQueen!
ദ്ധ-ഡണണ ക ല്ധാധണ, [ഠിക്്ഴിറ്വേബ്‌
Free Bird!
“8ധഡ്വ൭ 8ലാമട്‌
You know, the Rust-eze Medicated Bumper Ointment team
ഉടടടധിക്സഖ് ലാം ്ട്ലം
ran a great race today.
0൨൭ ഹാലിധ്സാബണയാിഗ്ലി ല്‍.
And remember, with a little Rust-eze...
൭, 990 ട൦൦॥൩ ്ടല..
And an insane amount of luck,
൧൭ ൦ ന്൯ട്വാവര്‍ 01൦.
.-you too, can look like me. Ka-chow.
രവ ാഠ01ല൨ ന്ഥ ടലോല ലിവ. ലാട
- Hey, kid. - We love ya.
- ല്‍, ധി. - ദ്ര ടൃാ(യ്ബിത്ഖ.
And we're looking forward to another great year.
ഉസ്‌ നലഘാന്മ്ല്വിത്ന ട്ധ മഠ ഡണ൪൭ ലാട
Just like this year!
ഭല്യാലന്‍ ഥി!
Not on your life.
1ലിഗ്ഥാനന.
- Don't drive like my brother! - Yeah, don't drive like my brother!
- എത്്രാാധ നാ ലാ വ!
California, here we come!
ടഗ്ഠബട, (ഒ൦ റ്റെ
Dinoco, here we come!
൧0൦0, യി ്ദ്്!
I needed this. Hello?
൨, ല്വവാല്ധിത്നബ്‌
Is this Lightning McQueen, the world's fastest racing machine?
വ്‌ നഗ !൧൩൧൭ ൧൭൧൦ (ദയ വന വഥ്വഒ
Is this Harv, the world's greatest agent?
ബലം ണന ലാന ബട?
it almost hurts to take ten percent of your winnings.
(൭൦0൭൧ നലറ൭7൧ 70% റ്൭7്‌ (കനഹെറ്ററെ (൪൧.
Merchandising. And ancillary rights in perpetuity. Anyway, what a race, champ!
൧ുഒഗ ൧ഖ7ററ്ററ 070770. ഥു ൧൭ല൭സ്ാണഗെെ. £ലധ്്ഥദ ൭ ഗലാദ.
! didn't see it, but I heard you were great.
൧൧ ൭൭ഥ൨റ൦% ഒ്ല7 ൭:൨൧ റ്ഠാററ്റല (രഥ ലാട!.
Thanks, Harv.
ലിനാ ടി, [1
Listen, they're giving you 20 tickets for the tiebreaker thing in Cali.
77ഥാഴ്‌ (ഒ൧ 20 7൭ ശ്ാലഗ്മ്ാഥാദണ റെ.
I'll pass ‘em on to your friends. Shoot me the names.
൧൧ ഖര്ഥ ഗഗ ൧ടഠ്ദ (ഒ്സ൭ഥ-ക്സഥ (രഥ. ലന ഖധ ഗന ന്റ്‌
- You let Harv rock it for you. - Right. Friends.
൭, ഖധബ്ത്ഷമ.
Yes, there's...
[ഗി0ഠഠിഠിലി...
OK, I get it, Mr. Popular.
൧ഥല്ഥലന.
So many you can't even narrow it down. Hey, when you get to town,
7ഖല്‌ഖ 7 ഒഥ ഒ ഥ്ദ്ഥാടറലനഗ ൧9 (ഒഥാക്‌ഗകഗ,
you better make time for your best friend!
7ഗഥറര്ഥ നടേ ശ്വ ൦൧ രഥ്‌
Break bread with your mishpocheh here!
ഗഗ്൭ നലഭ്ഥ ൧2ല5൭൦൩൭.
That'd be great! We should totally...
ലാട! 9..
OK, I gotta jump, kid. Let me know how it goes. I'm out.
7ഖ൧൭൭൭ ഠാലഡ്യ. 2ലസ്ഖഥ ഒധ കാശ്ഥമ്ഥ ൧ ഗഗ. ലെന 0റ00൭..
What? A minivan?
൧൭ ഗാഥ ന്ബ്‌
Come on, you're in the slow lane. This is Lightning McQueen you're hauling.
൧), 709൨ 4ക൧ ഥലദഭറ്ട വ്‌ !൧70ററ 0ല൭0൭൨.
Just stopping off for a quick breather, kid.
ലവ ാല്നന്‌ ലാലല ടലഭ്യ്യാ.
- Old Mack needs a rest. - Absolutely not.
൧൧ലലലപനച്പ അല ച സ്വാ ഒഷ്ധ
All night? May I remind you federal DOT regs state...
ടല്ോദബ്ുനാ ന്ല്ണ്‌? 8ഠില മിവ സമത ത്ധ,ലാല്ഡന ഥ0ഠെ..
Come on, I need to get there before Chick and hang with Dinoco.
൧൧ ൧൭൧ ഒന്വാല്‌ ലോല്ഥന ൨൨ല റ്റ !൭൨റ 7൭൭5൭ റ്റ്ഗ ൧:0ഠ00൧.
All those sleeping trucks.
ലന്ധാ നിവ്യ പ.
Hey, kid, ! don't know if can make it
൧൧൭ലഥഥ ട൭നടറ്9 20'൦ ഗാല്ലാെ.
Oh, sure you can, Mack.
1ലന്ധവാഠിലി, [ഗമ
Look, it'll be easy. I'll stay up with you.
൧ഡാലിദാദ ഠ്ബത്ധ.
- All night? - All night long.
- ക്ല്ാാടറഥറ നട(ഒന 7 - ലോ നമല്ണ.
- Hey, yo, D.J. - What up?
- യാ റില്ല, ൧.7 - യാ റ്ല്വാല?
We got ourselves a nodder.
ഗ്മ 9 ഭല്ട നല്റാന്ധിം
Pretty music.
ടലഠില്വാ സ്ധമിധ്ബി.
Yo, Wingo! Lane change, man.
നധിയ്വ ൦൭൭.
- Right back at ya! - Yeah!
ര ം്ുഭാദ്ധി!
- Cops! I missed. - You going on vacation?
- കിണി 1പടാടല. - [ദ്ര നിലാ ലാലി?
- Oh, no, Snot Rod... - He's gonna blow!
- ൨, ഠി - ഠാ 31൭൩ നല്ട്ല്‌
Gesundheit!
ലാറു ടല
One should never drive while drowsy.
1ലിലാമ്ഡ്‌നനമ്ഥ്ധ ടണടട നല്റമന്ധം
Mack!
[ഗീ
Hey, Mack! Mack!
[ഴീദഠറ ൨൦।, 72൮ [ഗി
Mack, wait for me!
ഗീ സ്ഥാ ലയി
Mack!
[ഗീ
Mack! Mack...
[ഗഗ
..wait up! Mack.
ഗീ സഥാ്ധ!
What? You're not Mack.
൧൧൭൦ ദ്ധ ാധിഖ്ബഴിദലറ
Mack? I ain't no Mack! I'm a Peterbilt, for dang sake!
ഗി ചവവാധിത്ബഴിദലറ എവ ലല്ലബി
Turn on your lights, you moron!
ഉടടടു ്വാധത്ധ, ഠഠ൦)
Mack... The Interstate!
ഗി. ഠി ലാധിന്മ ന്പ്ട്മല്‍!
Not in my town, you don't.
ദ്ധ 0൦16൩0൮൭ 0ലാബ ഠി 0 മവ.
Oh, maybe he can help me!
൨, സ്ഥി1ന൩ ഠദ 00൦1൦011൦0 മയി
He's shooting at me! Why is he shooting at me?
(രന്ല്വാട ഠി സാലഡ്‌!
l haven't gone this fast in years.
ഉണ ല്വടിലില്ാല്റ്ബി.
I'm gonna blow a gasket or somethin’.
പ്ൂംസ ടലിറ്ലധിട.
Serpentine! Serpentine, serpentine!
ദ്ച്ത്നധി ങ്ക ധി
What in the blue blazes?
൧൧൭ ധി വധ?
Crazy hot-rodder.
ലററ 9॥9
I'm telling you, man, every third blink is slower.
൧൮ ഠയ്വാവാദ്ധി, ടലില്വാ ഭാമ ിലാവ്വാലിദ്്ഥ.
The sixties weren't good to you, were they?
1ടസ്ഥ 60-0 ല്വാലിധിലയ്ധ, കന?
What? That's not the Interstate!
൧൭൦ ൮ ാധിത്ബിലാധ്ന്ുര നടല്‍!
I'm not the only one seeing this, right?
ധി മിവ ടം നന്പാട്പത്ന?
- Incoming! - Whoa, man.
്വല്ട നല്ക!
- No! - Hey!
- ഠി - ല്‍!
My tires!
1ദുദ്വ മിവ!
Fly away, Stanley. Be free!
ഹാഖ, ടബിഖ. ഒലാമടിത്ഥ 0!
Boy, you're in a heap of trouble.
ച്പനല്പാടടല്‌ നടടല്ലന ന്ധ.
We're live at the Los Angeles International Speedway
൧ 7൭൦ ൧൧൭ഖ്ഥാഴഥെറ്റടട 05 ൧൧റുലഒെ, ൧ല൭൩൭..
as the first competitor, Lightning McQueen,
൧ലഗ്ഥാട ഥാല്ഖനട ..7ഗഒ 770...
is arriving at the track.
...൧൭.
Is it true he's gonna pose for Cargirl?
- ഠ്ഒരഗ ാഖ്ഥ്‌ ന്ദ നഗ ഒ - ൧൧9 50949൮ രഥ്‌
What? Did I forget to wipe my mud flaps?
൧൧൭7 ൧൮ 4൧0൭ ഒ00 ൧൩൧൧ ന്‌ ൧ല907റ7്‌
McQueen's driver arrived in California, but McQueen was missing.
൧ലനദറ്ഥിറേലൈ ൧൭ (ഒഥ൧ാഥ൮൭
- McQueen was reported missing. - .,to race an unprecedented...
- ഥ്ല്ഗ്നഥഒ 70ലേധെ 7ഒററ്റ - ൧9 വ്ഒറ്ധലത്ഥ ൧ഖ്൧൩൧൭...
Sponsor stated they have no idea where he is.
൧റെടഒവഒ ഥല്ര്ട സഥ്ല്ടലഥഥ ന്‌ നട വ്ഒ ൧ലഒറ്ഒ.
l hope Lightning's OK. I'd hate to see anything bad happen to him.
ച്വിഘ്വാ 190 ലാലിദ്വാധസിധാലില്വ ബു.
1 don't know what's harder to find, McQueen or a chief who'll work with him!
൧൧൭ ) (ലാ47 ഗര വ്‌൦൭൦, 77ഗഥലേധെ ൭19൧ (൭൧൭ ഗ7ഗെ)൭ മേറററഥ ക്ല ഗ്റ്വൃഭ?
Lightning McQueen must be found at all costs!
ഗഗ ി7ഥേഥൈ നടെ വ്ൃധ്ന്യാല്‌.
They're all asking the same question: Where is McQueen?
77 ടബണട ൧ലഒ൧൮)൭ 50൭(൭൧ 1 597൭, വ്‌ നറ ലേ?
Where am I?
ഉ നന്മ ദിവ്‌?
Mornin’, sleepin’ beauty!
ലന്‌ ഠാ!
Boy, was wonderin’ when you was gonna wake up.
എിവാഥ സ്ഥാ 0॥യ്ധ ന്ധധാാഥ.
Take whatever you want! Just don't hurt me!
എസ്ബാ॥ ല്വായ്ധ ന്റ്‌ റവന്യൂ േഠില്ലിയ്ഥ ലിവ്‌
A parking boot? Why do I have a parking boot on?
(രന്ല്വാ ഒഖ ലിവ ഠിഡ്ണല്‌?
l like you already. My name's Mater.
൧൮ ഠ്ല്വാധന ടിവി ത്ധ. പ്ൂംണ3 ലവ ഴിദ്ല.
Mater?
ഗിമ്ല?
Yeah, like "tuh-mater," but without the "tuh".
[ഗീഠഠന “ഡന-നദ്ല്‌ ദ്വി ൭109 “ഡന്‌.
- What's your name? - You don't know my name?
- ടില്യാാ നന ത്ധ? - [ദ്ര 1ടിവല്ഡ നണട ദിവ?
No, I know your name. Is your name Mater too?
1 1-111-17 1-111-11:
Look, I need to get to California as fast as possible. Where am I?
ചവവാലിധിഭ 041 ടലലാ്‌ സ്ധഘാ!ന൬൩. 2 നന്മ ദവ?
Where are you? Shoot!
ഉ നാന്മത്ധ?
You're in Radiator Springs.
ദ്ധ ഠി "ടടിഗ്മഠിക്ല.
The cutest little town in Carburetor County.
ഒം !൭൦॥ ഠി ലല ഠഹാധഖം.
Oh, great. Just great!
ലാട. ധന്യാഥ് ലാല്‍
Well, if you think that's great, you should see the rest of the town.
ദ്രിദ്ധിത്ധ ടാ ലാഖ്‌, ദ്ധവാദ്ഡ്‌ 1ല001ഠല്ന്ാബില്നാന്ച ബ്‌.
You know, I'd love to see the rest of the town!
ദ്ധ ലിസ, ലവണ നവാംഗല്മ്യാബില്റാന്ച ബ്‌!
So if you could just open the gate, take this boot off,
ദ്വിദ്ധത്ധവാധിര ഗാല ഠബബിഡാ ആഖല്ലി,
you and me, we go cruisin’, check out the local scene...
റമ 0൧01ല്‍ ലാല്യി 101 ലിവ്ഗി ന്വാട്ല.
- Dad-gum! - How'd that be, Tuhmater?
കിണി -ഗീമനാന്മു?
- Cool! - Mater!
- ലാണ്‌ -ഗീമ്ലി!
What did I tell you about talkin’ to the accused?
൧൧൭ മവിത്ട ന്ഥണ് ലയ്വാ 0 യു ഠി?
To not to.
ടന്്പാന്യ്ലിത്വാ.
Well, quit your yappin' and tow this delinquent road hazard to traffic court.
19ഠി വാണ 0ദ്യ്വാ ദന വ്നഠ്ടാടടടില് ബ്‌ ഭ നദ്വി ലിം
Well, we'll talk later, Mater.
ദ്മവാല്ടന്ധാറാ ഭസ്ധാ।.്ീമ്ല.
"Later, Mater." That's funny!
ലന്ധഠന, ഗ്ല. ധേ!
The Radiator Springs Traffic Court will come to order!
ഗിംവിയനല്വ് ജിടി ടിയ്ബാണ്്ധില!
Hey, you scratched my paint! l oughta take a blowtorch to you, man!
ദ്ധ ദില്‌ മ ലിവ്‌!
You broke-a the road! You a very bad car!
ദ്ധ നടലിറിയ്ബ്യടി്ബ്‌ 'ധ്ധ ക്ല
- Fascist! - Commie!
- മട്ട! - രരന്ധബ്ട!
Officer, talk to me, babe. How long is this gonna take?
ബി ലിവ വമ്പ നടടട്വാല്ഘ്വാ ണമ?
I gotta get to California, pronto.
ചവന 1ഭ 041൦ ടു.
Where's your lawyer?
[ഗി ാഠറ്ധാണ ത്വ?
I don't know. Tahiti maybe. He's got a timeshare there.
ഗ്ധ്ിന൩ ൦ നല്വ. ൧19 30൭ 31ഘ് ലഗ്ന ഠി ടമ.
When a defendant has no lawyer, the court will assign one to him. Hey!
8॥0॥നഅിഗാല്ട്ക ലാട ാല്വേണ, നട്വിയ്നല ല്ത്ന ഡാടടിത്ന ടട ധനു.
Anyone want to be his lawyer?
൧൧൭ ടടടി്യാ നലിധുഠി വാഠറ്ധണ ഠി?
Shoot, I'll do it, Sheriff!
819911, ലിവ ടിയ്നട്ഡിക്ഥ, ടര്‌!
All rise! The Honorable Doc Hudson presiding.
ലന്ധപാബാഥ്ബ്‌ ബാ ്ഥംം റല്ധാ്ടംന ടയബാട്ച്്ഞ്!
Show-off.
ലിമി
- May Doc have mercy on your soul. - All right,
നനഠറടമ ൧൦ ൭ടി്ബിദ്്ധ.
l wanna know who's responsible for wreckin' my town, Sheriff.
ടില്വാധാനാറാഗഥ്ഘയ്ദഘാ നല്ഠടട്റയ്ാലഠ്ല ലവ, മല്‌?
l want his hood on a platter!
എവ നലിഗസ്പടന്മ്വ്ത് ഠി!
I'm gonna put him in jail till he rots! No, check that.
൧൮ മിയ്ബ്വാബുദ്ല്ത്ഥ ദ വ്ന്യാദ ഠദ ലാഥ്‌ ന്യ വ.
I'm gonna put him in jail till the jail rots on top of him,
വനാ ഘ്്ഖ്ട ല്വാധ്‌,
and then I'm gonna move him to a new jail and let that jail rot.
ഭന്ധഠിക്ന 0നാ്മ്ല്‍്ത്ഥ ഠദഭ ഹവ്്ല്ലാബസ ്ബിലിത്ഥ ഹല്ല ധാ ്വാഥി
I'm...
൧൮...
Throw him out of here, Sheriff.
ന്വാലിറിദ ക്ല ഠി ട്വ, ട്ഘന്‍്‌.
I want him out of my courtroom. I want him out of our town!
11:11: :11:18111-1
- Case dismissed. - Yes!
(൫5 ഠിറ്ധാധിത്ത്‌
Boy, I'm purty good at this lawyerin' stuff.
൧൮ റുവാദാധട ഠ്ണിഘി ണമ ബ്‌.
Sorry I'm late, Your Honor!
[ഗാ വിസാ, ഥാ ഗണി
Holy Porsche! She's gotta be from my attorney's office.
1ല്വ ഠി ഠി ലവ ലധമണ 1൮.
Hey, thanks for comin’, but we're all set.
[ഗ് ഠ11 ട൭ഠിഒ.
- He's letting me go. - He's letting you go?
- ൧9 ലിദ്നിലാടട(ക്ന ടവ. - [1 ല്ാമടിത്ന ത്വ?
Yeah, your job's pretty easy today.
(വ്വ സ്വഠ്ല്ന്ലി ബ്‌.
All you have to do now is stand there and let me look at you.
ദ്ധ ഡ്മ ാലിധാവല മവ ഘുംത്ഖ.
Listen, I'm gonna cut to the chase. Me, you, dinner.
൧വാാലല്‍റമ്ന ൦. ദ്ധ ൦ മവ നിത നല്ണ.
- Please! - know. I get that reaction a lot.
- 101൦! -൧ിവ ടല ഠ്വ ലഭി.
I create feelings in others that they themselves don't understand.
൧വ വടി മട ാദഠ്ദ ൦ ഴു സട ടിവ്ല്മ്ണ.
Oh, I'm sorry. Did I scare you?
ഗാ. ചവ ടിഡത്ലിത്ധ?
A little bit, but I'll be all right.
൭൦ഠി॥൨, ദ്വ 31൮ 1൭10൨ ല്ാമ-ദ്വാമ.
OK. I'm gonna go talk to the judge.
8:10. ൧൮ ടിബാനയലിത്വാ ഠ്ന്ബ്ഘ്ന്ന.
Do what you gotta do, baby. But listen. Be careful.
1ടിയിത്ന ല്വാവയ ലാല്ധ. ല്ല ൫.
Folks around here are not firing on all cylinders, if you know what I mean.
[ഴില്മി വാലാധഠ്ധിി ട്വ 1ടിലാല്റ്ഖ ടി.
Ka-ching!
ചിന
I'll keep that in mind.
1-111-14
- Hey there, Mater. - Howdy, Sally.
- ല്‍, [ഗിീദ്‌ല - യാ റില്ല, ടല
- Hi, folks! - Good morning!
൨ ടന്ധമ!
You know her?
!ദ്ധിഭ്ന3 ഠി?
She's the town attorney and my fiancée.
൧1 ാല്ധ്പാഖ്്ല ബ്‌ ഠ്‌ ഡാ മവ.
Nah, I'm just kiddin’. She just likes me for my body.
എവ ാല്യ്ധ്ധ. ൧1൭ ൯൫0൭ ടധിരിയ്വ ലിവ ടലാലാ ഡാധി മിവ.
You look great. You do something different with your side view mirrors?
൧൦൦, ൭൨ ൪ലന്വാദലഘാദ്‌. !ദ്ധില്വിത്ന ടല്ധ്ധാടഠിട ലേന്ന്നലാ। ദ്ധ?
What do you want, Sally?
൧൭ ജം ടമ
Come on, make this guy fix the road. The town needs this.
1 :1::111:11:111 ദം ബി ലാല്ധി്സ.
No. I know his type. Racecar.
100 ഷയഭ്നബട ദ. ലഭ ധ്സാദ.
That's the last thing this town needs.
ദലം ഘഖിന്നുരാഖ്്ല ബ്‌ ല്ധിത്വ.
OK, I didn't want to have to do this, Doc, but you leave me no choice.
൧൮ ലിഗന്ലവ്ധദ്വാല്റ്ല്‍ി, ദ്വ യ്വ 19വാലി ലിവ നഅ്ബില്ല.
Fellow citizens, you're all aware of our town's proud history.
ലറാ്ധഠധിം്ധമ,ഖ്്ഖ ടടഠില 1ല്മനൂ ടല്ല്മ്വിഭ്ാാഘാബാഖ്ണ്‍്ല ബ്‌.
Here she goes again.
൧19 510 സ്വ.
Radiator Springs, the glorious jewel
1ടടിാഠിഖഠ, സ്ധ്ല്ട ബ്ല
strung on the necklace of Route 66, the mother road!
ലില്ലധ്ടട മണലി ഠ। പട 66, ടബധ്ണട!
It is our job and our pleasure to take care of the travelers
൧൭1510 ഡാദട ന്മ നബ്ബിമാമ ശ്വാല്ിയ്ബ്വാണാണ്ഡാമ്ദ
- on our stretch of that road. - Travelers? What travelers?
൮൬൭ നല്ലിധ ടി. - ബുബ്പാല്മ ല്ലാ?
Ignore him.
പത്ബ്വാടഠ്ധി॥ത്ഥ ഠഒ.
But how, I ask you, are we to care for those travelers
ലാ ാറമ്നന്മന്ട ന൭10നബ്ു്റ ന്ന.
if there is no road for them to drive on?
ചിര ടലി ഥിന്ന്റ്‌
- Luigi, what do you have at your store? - Tires.
-ധി॥, 3 3ഠി9 ഠി ഭഠ്ലി ദ്വ? - ഖൃദ്വ.
And if no one can get to you?
ഉ രദ്ധ മമ ടിദ്വാ 0ഠില ടന്വാട! ൫ ഭാ ത്വ?
I won't sell any... tires. I will lose everything!
എവ ലിഗില്വാബ്ധി! ഒ. ൧൮ മിത്വിണു ടാലി!
- Flo, what do you have at your store? - [have gas.
- 6൦, ട്വ 3ഠി9 ഠി ഭഠ്ലിധ്വ? -൧ിവ ദ്ദ സസ്യ
- Lotsa gas! - OK boys, stay with me.
[ഗസ്സ - £ഠവട ല്വാദ മിവ ൭9.
And, Flo, what'll happen if no one can come to your station to buy gas?
൦, ല്വാദ ാലിദവിയ്ിദ്ധ 19% 0ഠില ഖ്യു 0൧൦ സ്സ്‌
I'll go outta business and... we'll have to leave town.
ടട മവ ടിയബാദഖ്ബിന്ല്വാ ൭൦൩ ൭1൮൨ ണാം ാദിത്ഥാ്ച ബ്‌.
What's gonna happen if Flo leaves town and closes her station?
ഉ ല്വാദ ലിദ്വ ഥാലിദിവ ദ്ധ ലം ഡ്്വിഭാല്ബു?
- Without gas, we're done for! - What?
ബാ സ്സഖ്പഘാടിട്വിന്ട!
Don't you think the car responsible should fix our road?
പ്ടഠിാധിക്ബിക്വിവട്മു ലാറാ ാമ്ഡ്പാലിറ്ല്ബന്മ?
The only guy strong enough to fix that road is Big Al!
1310൮ ഡിഡ്വാവട്‌ വാലി ്ധല്ം ലച!
Lizzie, the guy left, like, 15 years ago.
മ്മം, ഠി ഠ്ദ്വ്യാ്ി! 15൩ ഠ്വ.
Then why are you bringing him up, you lemon?
പഠി (ഒല്വാ ടലാധ്‌ മയ! 1ല്മനൂ ഠി, 000൦17
Oh, he can do it.
൭൨, റിാഠില്വാധമ!.
He's got the horsepower. So, what do you want him to do?
൭൨, ഠദ ഡിഡ്വാ വട. പഠി ച്വാന്ധ നവി ാധദ്റ്‌
Fix the road!
ചിറി!
- Because we are a town worth fixing! - Yeah!
ലാലാ ാ0ഠ്ല ।ന്ടവാല്മഠ്വാലി!
Order in the court!
ലവ.
Seems like my mind has been changed for me.
പുംസ്ഥലിസ ന്ഥ ലിവ ല്ല ഠ്വ.
Nice ruling.
ലലറ്റ്ഘ്ന്ന്സ൪ 1
lam so not taking you to dinner.
ചവ മിഗന്ലധാഴയ ത്വ നല്ക നല്ണ.
That's OK, Stickers. You can take Bessie.
1ഒണലുല്വാമ. ദ്ധാഠില്വാദ്ധ 8ടടടില.
Man, you get to work with Bessie!
!ദ്ധാഠില്വാലഷ്ട 0 8ടടടില്‍!
I'd give my left two lug nuts for somethin’ like that.
൧൮ ടാാധാാധദ് ലാട ടയ ധി.
Bessie? Who's Bessie?
ടട? ടില്വാദ 8ടടടില?
This here is Bessie, finest road-pavin' machine ever built.
1 ദ 8ടടടില, നടട്ബാലിറ[ല്ന ൮൮ 0510 ലാന 19.
I'm hereby sentencing you to community service.
ദ്ധ ഠിന്ധ്ധണ ॥ധാ്ധടധസ്ണട നടഷ്ിയ്‌.
What? This place is crazy!
൧൧൭! 7ന്വാദ ബി ദ!
I know this may be a bad time right now,
ഗ്രന ബ നടു ടട.
but you owe me $32,000 in legal fees.
90 ദ്ധ ദിവ യ ധേ്മന ടലാസ൭32,000.
We're gonna hitch you up to Bessie, and you're gonna pull her nice.
ദരി ടിക്ബിഭ്ന്മിത്ിത്ധ 0 ദ്ടടടില ്ബത്ധ ടിക ഥ്ന്മ്ക്ന ഠി ഠി
You gotta be kidding me.
ന്ധ ത്ധാദ്യ്്ത്വ.
You start there where the road begins.
ദ്ധ സ്ധിദ ഠി ടമ, ഠി നാന്ദി ന്ധി.
You finish down there where the road ends.
ദ്ധ ലാിടിത്ഥ ഠി ടി, ഠി നാന്ലവടിാട്ലിന്പ.
Holy shoot!
ചിന
Whoa, whoa, whoa! How long is this gonna take?
ദലഘ്വാ ണാ ടിക സാ നട്ട?
Well, fella does it right, should take him about five days.
ദ്രിദ്ധ വ ഠണ്ബോബ്ബി, ്ല്ണ ന ൫൨0.
Five days?
ല്ണ്ജഘി!
But I should be in California schmoozing Dinoco right now!
൧വവാദ്ധഡ ഠം ഠി ഗണി, സ്ഥ ൧1000)
Then if l were you, I'd quit yappin' and start workin"!
ദ്രിദ്ധ ലാ ലല്‌ ലാലിയ ൦ സ്ധിദ ല്ലി!
- Hook him up, Mater. - Okay-dokey.
- ഉദടംാിത്ഗ ഠിം, [ഗീ്ല. - 819൨.
Freedom!
(്വാലാടടദ്ബ്‌
Maybe I should've hooked him up to Bessie...
ഗ്ധ്ിന്൬൩ ല്വവാഖ്ഡ്‌ ഗടാ(ത്ന ഠി വാദ 8ടടടി..
..and then... then took the boot off.
൧ ാധിര ഡം മഖന്സഒ.
Goodbye, Radiator Springs, and goodbye, Bessie!
ലന 09, "ഒടി ൦൮൦0 ൦ ടലനമ ധാ 8ടടടില്‍!
California, here l come! Yeah!
ബ്ദ, ബി ലവ ദാ!
Oh, feel that wind.
൨, ടടലിത്ന ബ്ബ.
Yes!
1 1)
No. No, no, no.
19%
No, no, no, no, no. Outta gas?
്്ല്വ്ട സ്ബൂഖ്റ
How can I be outta gas?
ഗീഠഠണാന്വാഠില്വിഘാട സ്സ
Boy, we ain't as dumb as you think we are.
ദ്രബിവാധിക്ന ടലാഠഠ്ംസുഴുയ്വ ടബാ(൭.
But how did, how did... you...?
ലി ാട്റുമ്നട്മ്‌?
We siphoned your gas while you were passed out.
ദി ഭ്ധലിത്ഥ സ്സ ടലനദടമ ദ്ധ വാലുട.
Ka-chow.
ലിച്ചി!
- Gentlemen. - Sheriff.
- വവ - ല്‌
Hey, Sheriff.
൦, ടണ്‌.
- Why tires here? - Sono sempre stati qui.
(രന്ല്വാട ദുഖ ൦9 ഠ। ടബ്‌?
- They were better before. - Stai sempre a parlare.
1ലാവാലിഠ്(ന്വാമിത്ഥ ടല ഠ്ഥ്വ.
- Guido! - Red, can you move over?
നം. - ലാ, ഭല!!
I want to get a look at that sexy hot rod.
൧൮ ന്ല്വലംഭഷ്ഭ ടലദ വ.
You know, I used to be a purty good whistler.
ഉല്ല മവവാഖ്നാല ഠാല്ട്ധി.
I can't do it now, of course, on account of sometimes
ലന്നു ഒ0ധിലീ ടലാദ്ധാ മഠിദ ഠേ...
I get fluid built up in my engine block,
.൧ലിവന്ധാധി ഠി൩ 01൦1 ലബ്ന മിവ,
but Doc said he's gonna fix it. He can fix about anything.
ഉത നമി. ൧19 0ഠ1ല്വാദ॥ദി ല്വാദ ട്വ.
That's why we made him the judge.
ലാലാ വ ഖ്്പ്ദഠിത്ഥ ദ നിന്ന.
Boy, you shoulda heard me on Giddy-up, Oom Papa Mow Mow.
!ദ്ധവാദ്ധഡ്ഠ്നണ്യ മിവ നബി.
Now, I'm not one to brag
ധി ന്ധവാല്നടട,
but people come purty far to see me get low on the "Mow-Mow".
ദ്വ ണി ഠാ ദ്ധി നിഹാല്‌ മവ നസി.
- Man, that's just great! - Hey, what's wrong?
- ൭൨൨ നനാ ലാട! - (രനല്വാദ?
My lucky sticker's all dirty.
ലലിലയ്ലാലസ്പല മിഡിയ
That ain't nothin’. I'l clean it for ya.
1519 0൭. ൧ഡാാല്ടിവിക്ന ധിലത്ഖ.
That won't be necessary.
1ലിലാല്ധാധദ്വാല്റ്ഡ
Hey! Hey, big fella! Yeah, you in the red!
ലല! മ, ദ്ധ ലാസ നല്‌
I could use a little hose down. Help me wash this off.
8ഠില 11൦ ദ്നഥിത്ഥ? ടി ലല.
Where's he goin'?
[ഗി ഠി ന്മിഥാല്യി?
He's a little bit shy, and he hates you for killin’ his flowers.
൧19 ലാണദ്ധ ഠ്ബാല്ലിത്ത്ധ ടലാദ്ധ സ്വടന്മ്വി്ാഥാബുഒ.
I shouldn't put up with this.
എവ ലിവ! ണ ടസ്ഡം ബ്‌.
I'm a precision instrument of speed and aerodynamics.
൧൮ ഠിഠില ലിക്ല്യ്ന ൭൦ ലഠ്മ്നി
- You hurt your what? - I'm a very famous racecar!
- ദ്ധ ലോലിത ല്ാദ? 1-111-11.
You are a famous racecar? A real racecar?
!ദ്ധിഘഘ്ദധമ്പാദ ലിക്‌? ഘ്ടധ്ാാദ്ധി?
Yes, I'm a real racecar. What do you think? Look at me.
൮൭, മിധദ്ധല്ടിധ്പാലാഒ്ധി. 1൮.
l have followed racing my entire life. My whole life!
ചവ ॥ിഡി ടഥിത്നി്ധ്ാട ടല്ഥ് വ്ഠധോ വ. ടല്ധഡി വൊ ല്ഡ്‌
Then you know who I am. I'm Lightning McQueen.
പ്ഒഠി ധ്വനി ടല ൭1൮, [ഠിക്്ഴിറ്വേബ്‌
- Lightning McQueen? - Yes! Yes!
-[ഗീഠ്ധടല? ര്‍റ
I must scream it to the world!
൧൮ നട്ട്‌ [ണി തബവാദഠ്ദ ഥി!
My excitement from the top of someplace very high!
൫ല്വമന മിവ ലി ന്ഥബഈ൭ ടബമ്ന്ന്യാ..
- Do you know many Ferraris? - No, no, no, no, no.
ദ്ധി ാസഖ്ിഥ്ഷി?
They race on the European circuit. I'm in the Piston Cup!
1ഠിന്നഥിന ലയ. ചവ ഠിന ലം ലിട്ഥബ്‌
- What? - Luigi follow only the Ferraris.
ധി! ബന ॥വി ലിസാ ണ്ടി.
Is that what I think it is?
൧1൨ ബ ലാ വ ടടലിത്ന?
Customers.
ലലാ.
Customers! Customers, everyone! Customers!
ലലാ ൧ല്‍ബ്യാന, ടസ്ഡല്‍!
- OK! - Customers?
ലലാ
It's been a long time. Remember what we rehearsed.
ധാ ലനാ! റവന നമ്‌ ലാഭ ന്൯ ഠ്ല്വാലിട.
Make sure your "Open, please come in" signs are out.
ലലാ, “ദധി, ടി [ഗ്മ ഠി ധ്‌.
You all know what to do. All right, nobody panics. Here we go!
ദ്ധ ലിസ ല്വാ നലിഗധ്ധ. ഷുഡ്‌ നസ്ധിട്ത്ല്‍്‌
Van, I just don't see any on-ramp anywhere.
ഒ , മിവ 51ഗന്വാ ട്ര ഠി നന്ന.
- Minny, I know exactly where we are. - Yeah, we're in the middle of nowhere.
[ഗിന്നസ്‌ മിവ ല്ഡ ഠി നടന. - ൭, ണ്ട്‌ ന്മ.
- Honey, please. - Hello.
- 101൦1510 ട്വ. - 11610.
Welcome to Radiator Springs, gateway to Ornament Valley.
ലണ്ട്‌ ബ്നു ഭ 1ടടിഗ്മഠിക്ല,
Legendary for its service and hospitality.
1ലിഭന്മി! 9൩0 ൧ലമ്പണ്ണമ്മ്ന ലലിവല്ന്‌ ്്ബ്വാല്ണമ.
How can we help you?
ദില്‌ ാന്ധ?
- We don't need anything, thank you. - Ask for directions to the Interstate.
1ഠില്ലിനട യടി.
There's no need to ask for directions. I know where we're going.
എവ ലിഥാല്ധ ഡബ്ധിധ്യ. എവ ല്ധിഭ നന്മ 9 ാല്യ!.
He did the same thing on our trip to Shakopee.
൧19൨ ലാലിത്ധടു ടണം ടണടടമ ഗലി ഖ്്ി ഭ ടിജിര്വാട.
We were headed over there for the Crazy Days, and we...
വ്രണ നല്റല്ട ഭ ഗ്മ ൧ ഠ൭0..
- OK. Really. We're just peachy, OK? - What you really need
- ദ്ര ാദിഗല്യ, ഠ്യ? - യാ ൮൬ ത്ധവാലിധ്ത്ന
is the sweet taste of my homemade, organic fuel.
13ില്വിഭന്മ്യ്ഥ സ്സദ്ു്ിം വട്ട ബന ലിവ.
No, it doesn't agree with my tank.
19 1൭10 ടടട്ധല 0 1ി1ഠ ടവ.
- Just trying to find the Interstate. - Good to see you, soldier!
ദരി ടി നാലി ലാധ്ന്മര സ്ഭ.
Come on by Sarge's Surplus Hut for your government surplus needs.
ഉ്ാടനിഭ കാല ഷ്ണ 0ധിശ്വാലിധബാല്യ്ിലാന്.
- Honey, surplus! - We have too much surplus.
- ദയാ, ലാലാ. - [രമ മഠ ലില്ധാസതി്ലലാ।ന്മന.
I do have a map over at the Cozy Cone Motel.
൧൮ ഠി വാല ഠ। [70൦ ഠഠജു' ൭൦൫൭.
And if you stay, we offer a free Lincoln Continental breakfast.
ദ്രിദ്ധിത്ധ ലാല്‍ 9 ടന്മ, വ്വ ടലി ടലഘ്വാബ്വാല്ധണമ.
- Honey, she's got a map. - [don't need a map! I have the GPS.
- ൧8 ദഠ9 0൦൭. -൧ിവ ിലാല്ധിത്ാല്ട! ചവ ദഠ്ദ ൨05.
- Never need a map again, thank you. - How ‘bout somethin’ to drink?
ദറുല്നാന്മ ൦ സ്ധ്ഥണ്ണ്‌?
Stop at Flo's V-Eight Café. Finest fuel on Route 66.
ടഥഘഠ920 ൦ ൭്ര ശലം. ഗിസ്യാല്ന്യ എലി! വലി 66.
No we just topped off.
ദ്ര്ബിവാബടി സ്സ
And if you need tires, stop by Luigi's Casa Della Tires,
ദ്രിദ്ധ ാല്ധിത്ഥ ഒഖ, ട്ഘാഠമ ഠി ഭഠ്ലി ഷ്ട ൧൦൭ ൨ധ191..
home of the Leaning Tower of Tires.
൧1 നന്മ ബഖി ല്ഭ്ധടഥ ന്നാ.
- We're trying to find the Interstate. - But you do need a paint job.
- ദരസ്‌ നാലി ലാധ്ന്ര നട്ട. - ലാ ദ്ധ്വാല്ധ കേ ഠ്വ.
Ramone will paint you up right. Hey, anything you want!
ണം ലിന്വ ത്വ ബു േസ്പിം
- You know, like a flame job. - No thanks...
ഗീഠഠണധിറ്ട ല്വാ.
Maybe ghost flames!
ഗ്ധന്ിന്൩ ലവി ഥലിലസ്ധ!
You like old school pinstripin'? Von Dutch style?
ദ്ധ ടധിയട്ധ മണ ഠ്ധ്ധ? ദൃ ഗല്‌
Oh, honey, look. Von Dutch.
൭൨, ടഷത്റാ, ബം ഗ൦൦ ൧൧൧൩.
OK, no. We're gonna be going now, OK?
പ്പി, 10. ദരി നമായി ടല്യ്വ്ാ.
A little somethin’ to remember us by, OK?
ടടധദ്ധ ധിാദ്ലാഠ്ം യി, ലഭ
- OK! - Come back soon, OK?
ഉ 1.
Il mean, you know where we are! Tell your friends!
ദ്ധല്ധ ഠി നടന്മിയ്്ി ഥഠ്! ദം്മ്ഡിയയണിയ്മമ്്‌
Thanks again, folks. Bye-bye now.
ലന മടി ടട്യി 1 ടണ്ഡമ. ലമ ന്ന്യാല.
- [know how to get to the Interstate! - Do ya?
൧൮ ലി്ധാഠാല്നട്ട ന്വധവഭലാധ്ന്ുര
- Minny, no. - Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- 8ല്ധി? [ഗന്നം 0൩.
No, not really. But listen.
ലാലല 1.
I'm Lightning McQueen, famous racecar. I'm being held against my will.
൧ിവ [ഗിഠേധംറ, ദ്ഖ്മധസ്പാ ലിഭന്മി!. ൧൮ റിന്ന ഠി ടിബി ബാ ട9.
I need you to call my team, so they can come rescue me
൧ിവവാലിധിത്സിത്ധ സ്ധാഥാ ടിക ടവ, ട്ധ്യാദൃദ സ്ിലാഠില്‍ ടലണമിത്ഥ ടവ
and get me to California in time for me to win the Piston Cup. Understand?
ബാ മയിഭ 041൦.
No, it's the truth! I'm telling you! You gotta help me! Don't leave me here!
1ഠിപ്ഠിലിട ലാണ്‌ യ്ധ നട്‌ ഠിം ടവ! പാന ന്ന്യാലിത്ണ ട്വ!
I'm in hillbilly hell! My IQ's dropping by the second!
൧൮ ഠിന ലിയ! 10 ലവ നട്ഥസ്ഥ ടഖില്യാ ടമ
I'm becoming one of them!
൧൮ ഠ്ല്വദഠി നാണ സ്പിറ
OK, don't worry. They know where we are now.
ഗി0ില്ഡ ഠി നന്മ നാട ടല.
They'll tell friends. You'll see.
ഗി0ലിബാല്ല്ഡ ത്യ. ദ്ധ ബും ന്മ൬.
We'll be back for our Hank Williams marathon...
കമ്‌ ഒര്ഥ ൧൧൭൧൮, ഗഡ്‌ ൧൩൧൭ ൫൧ ഥ്൭ഥെലര്‍ഗ7ഒന...
- That's good. - ., after a Piston Cup update.
-[്ാറ്ധട - വ ഥാഗ്കന്ഥകഥറ്റട്ഥ !(റ(൭ഥറ 7൧൭(൭ ൧540൨.
Still no sign of Lightning McQueen. Chick Hicks arrived in California
79.57 7ഒറ്ട (ലഥ൭ 7൧. ഗ്വവഥലട ൧൭ ഗ്‌ ടഗ്ഠസട
and today became the first car to spend practice time on the track.
ശ്ഗമ്ഥടത്ഥ നടേ ഥല്ഒ വ്‌ ഒ
It's just nice to get out here before the other competitors.
ട്ലയഥഠ ടഒന്യാട! ലോലം ടഒഥറുറെ (ഒ൧.
You know, get a head start. Gives me an edge.
80൭ ൧൧൭! ൧ലട4ഒരാഒഥ. 28൭ ൭:൨ (൭:ലാ0൭൧.
Hey, McQueen... Eat your heart out.
൨൦, [ഗിഠേവം, നലിഖ്ഥ റമ്ധില്‌വ.
Let me get this straight.
810൭. ൫ ല്ലാ.
l can go when this road is done. That's the deal, right?
[ഗി്ല, മവ 0ഠ1ല0 ലയി ദഖ്നി ടല. ഖവാലി?
- That's what they done did said. - OK. Outta my way.
-[ധി്വട്വ്സമ. - ഠധാദ്ധിഭലാ!.
I got a road to finish.
൧൮ നലി:ടില്യിയ്ബ്ട്ണ.
- He's done! - Done?
൧19 1 ട്വ!
It's only been an hour.
ടല്യാ? 8ബ ടല്ദ്ണ.
I'm done. Look, I'm finished.
ഉ ടിയാ. “ബം മവ 911 ടലടട!
Say thank you, and I'll be on my way.
റവന ധ്യാ നടന്‌ ൭൦൩ 1൮ മിതാലി.
- That's all you gotta say. - I'm the first one on the new road!
11111111: 1
It rides purty smooth.
ട്ടി മലമ.
- It looks awful! - Well, it matches the rest of the town.
- 19 ന്ഥി - ഉദഠിദ്ബി ബോല്‌ ബി.
Red.
[ഴില്ലി.
Who do you think you are?
ദ്ധ നാദത്വ ടില്ലാ?
Look, Doc said when I finish, I could go. That was the deal.
ഉഠഠത്്ട്വാ॥ഒ ടില്വാ മഡാഠില്വയാല്യി. ധവാല്ടബ്വ്ധന്സുഒ.
The deal was you fix the road, not make it worse.
ലലടല്ധ്യധ്സമം ത്വ ലിറ, ധിയ്ബ്ടഠി്സ ലാബി.
Now, scrape it off! Start over again.
ലിയ്വാവാധനെ. ഗ്ല ടണ്ഡി്ദ
Hey, look, grandpa, I'm not a bulldozer. I'm a racecar.
ഉല്ല ടി. 1-111-11
Is that right? Then why don't we just have a little race? Me and you.
ബ്ബ? പദഠി ലാ യദ നമ ധമ്സാദ?
- What? - Me and you. Is that a joke?
ദ്ധാാദ്യ്്ത്ധ?
If you win, you go and I fix the road.
ദ്രിദ്ധിത്ധ നന്മ, ലവി.
If l win, you do the road my way.
ദ്രിദ്ധ ലിവ നട്മു, ത്വാ ॥വ മര മിവ.
Doc, what're you doin'?
൧൦൦, ല്വാദ ദ്ധ ാധദ്റ്‌
I don't mean to be rude here,
ധി ന്വവിദ്ലാ, ൧൦൦.
but you probably go zero to sixty in, like, what? Three-point-five years?
ല്ല ദ്വ നലട്വാട! ന്൭ണ ധി ഠിന... ട ടബല്യുാ്ഥന്‌
Then I reckon you ain't got nothin’ to worry about.
ദ്രിദ്ധ ലാവ മാട ല്ലാ ഴു ര്ധാല്ധ റീടമ്ധ.
You know what, old-timer? That's a wonderful idea. Let's race.
ദ്ധ ലിസ ല്വാദ? ധഠിട ഴു ലാഖ്‌. ഷുഡ്നാലിധ്പാട.
Gentlemen, this will be a one-lap race.
ബി ഹലിധ്സാമമന ട്ബ ഹ്ധട്ാന.
You will drive to Willy's Butte, go around Willy's Butte and come back.
ദ്ധ ടി്ബ്വാബാധഭ ഗു ഒഥല, 1൪൭... ഭമ്ബാല। ടന്ധിട.
There will be no bumpin’, no cheatin’, no spittin’,
ടവല്‍ നല്ദന്യാല, നലല്‌. ..നല്ധഠ്,
no bitin’, no road rage, no maimin’,
നല, ടണടന്യുടിദ൩൨0..
no oil slickin’, no pushin’, no shovin’,
...നലഭമ്പാടടിന്ഥ സ്സ നലല
..and no lollygaggin’.
..ടധ നണ്ഡ്ധ നടെ
Speed. I'm speed.
(രിച്ന. ഷവ ലി ക്ല്ധ്ന.
Float like a Cadillac, sting like a Beemer.
ലഘ്വാധ് ന 3019൦, നു നന 8ടലനല[.
My friend Guido, he dream to give a real racecar a pit stop.
ദ്ധ ലവ ദധി, ന്ഥി ധം ടല്ഡ്ട (൭൭ ൩ ഠി ഘസ്ദ്ല്രാ.
The race is only one lap, guys.
ലലിധസ്ധാണ ബി ബന ട്ധ പട്ന.
Uno lappo! Don't need any help.
ദ്ധ ാധട്ുമ്ന്‌ എവ മിലാല്ധിത്ഥ സ്വ.
- Lwork solo mio, - Fine. Race your way.
-൧ിവ ാലഭ്ധ്ദ ടബാ(ന്ന. - 89൨. ॥വഖ്ജത്ഖ.
- No pit stoppo. Comprendo? - OK.
- 1ദധാടന. ലമ? - 819൨.
Gentlemen...
1:11]
..Start your engines!
.വിഠ്ധ്യിഖ് ബ്ന ്ം!
- jHijole! Check that out! - Whoa.
ധോദത്ധ നാല
Great idea, Doc. Now the road will never get done.
193൮൬ ലാട, ൧൦൦. ലന്ത ട്ല്വാ.
Luigi?
ധി?
On your mark, get set...
ലിമ ഠി റുിടന, ടഠഠിഒ..
Uno for the money, due for the show,
ടാഡ ലിഗ്‌ റ്ധ9 ധിറാല്ടന്പാട്..
tre to get ready, and quattro to... l can't believe it. Go!
19 ലാല്ടലഠിട, ൦ ലഎ്വാദ്‌.. ൧൮ മിലാ. ൧!
Doc... the flag means go.
൧൦൦, ലല്ല നലഭ്ധ്സുമയട്ദ.
Remember the fl... Here we go. Go.
എ! ഗ്൭ സ്ധില്ത്ഥ. ൭൭10.
Doc, what are you doing, man?
൧൦൦. ചാ ധ്ധാധദ്റ്‌
Oh, dear. It would seem I'm off to a poor start.
എിനല്ധ്ടല്വാ്സ് നി ഗന്ധി ധിം
Well, better late than never. Come on, Mater.
[ചാവാലി ലി ടറുലിബിാടഥാ. ചുഡ്പ്ഴ്മല.
- Might need a little help. - OK.
എവ സ്ഥാ ന്വാല്ധ്ഖ്ബാഖ്വദ.
You got your tow cable?
൧൧൭ ഷാല്‍ ഡ്മ ത്ധ?
Well, yeah, l always got my tow cable. Why?
ലസ്മടാ 3ഠി9. (ഒന്ല്വാമ?
Just in case.
൭൨, നാന്മ്ല്‌ മട്സതിദ്ധണ്ധ.
No, no, no, no, no!
ചിന
Bad trip, man.
ലല നനബഖിസിതക്ന.
Hey! Was that floatin' like a Cadillac or was that stingin' like a Beemer?
ലല! ഡ ലയ്വാഥ ന്ന 309൦ ട്വ നസാ നേന 8ലനല്‌?
I'm confused.
ച്യിര്ബ.
You drive like you fix roads.
ദ്ധ്വാബാധ നട ത്വാ.
Lousy! Have fun fishin’, Mater.
ലിറ ൭ല൦0001നനണമറഠ്ന്യ, 'റീദ്ല.
I'm startin’ to think he knowed you was gonna crash!
എവ ടാ ദ ്ഡ വ മിണ്ടാ
Thank you, Mater. Thank you.
ലിനാ !൭ട10, 'ഗീ്ല. ലന മടി.
Il can make a little turn on dirt.
൧ഡാഠില്വാധട്‌ ടല്‍ലര ദ്മടധന്വാഥ.
You think?
ദ്ധ ടമ?
No. And now I'm a day behind. I'm never gonna get outta here!
10% ടലയഷ്ാ വ ഠ്ല്വ്ഷ്്ന്യാല്ന ടാഡ 0. ഷവ ടിക ഠ92ക്ലല കട്ല!
Hey, ése! You need a new paint job, man!
!ദ്ധവാലിധിത്ന കാബ.
- No, thank you. - How 'bout some organic fuel?
- 1ഠിപ്ല്ട ൭ട॥൨ ട്വ. ഠി ന്സഖഗഥബിറ
- That freak juice? - Pass.
- പട ലവ? - 1ഒനലുല്ാമിട.
Watchin’ him is makin’ me thirsty. Anybody else want somethin’ to drink?
[ഴില॥നമ ഠി വാദ മിഡ്വട. ൭ടടില്വാഠ ന്ഥ്ഥണ്ണ്‌?
Nah, not me, Flo.
എവ ലിഗം
I'm on one of them there special diets.
൧൮ ടലി ഠി.
I'm a precisional instrument of speed and aero-matics.
൧൮ ഠിദിരലാഖ്ബഭ്ല്ധമ് ൦ ലന
"You race like you fix roads."
“യ്ധധമ്പാദ നട ത്ധവാദിധ്യട്ണ്‌
I'll show him. I will show him!
൧൮ മിക്ന ഡബ്ധിഠിത്ഥ ഹട ഠി!
Great! I hate it!
റപഘാ! ചവി!
- Hate, hate, hate, hate it! - Music. Sweet music.
- ലി! -ഗ്ധമിലള്‍്ധമിവുു നലന്മന്യിയ്വ.
Maybe this wasn't such a good idea.
ഗ്രന ബ 0ധിത്വഠ്ട൮൬൭ 31൦
Wow.
൧സ്ബാഠ।
Mornin’, Sally!
ലന 0, ടലി
Hey, look at this here fancy new road that Lightnin’ McQueen done just made!
ന്യുന ബബ നിം ൮9 'ഗീഠറ്ധ൦൦0 1 ട്ല്ധിഷ്വ്‌
Yes! Amazing!
൭ ഴിണ്ട്ദ്ധാിത്്‌
Ramone! Mama ain't seen you that low in years.
൭൨, ജനം! ൧ല്വാല്ല്ഥ ലിവ 1ടിവഹുംലത്ധ നല്ഥാധിട്ക്പ്ധ.
l haven't seen a road like this . In years.
ചവ ലിലും ടലാദ്റ്ബ ല്ലി.
- Well, then let's cruise, baby. - Low and slow.
- കൃവിവ്വാണ്യ! നണട. - ലാ ്ബ്വാലില്മ്ന.
x E bellissima! It's beautiful!
സിറ മാധ്‌ നിറ
Guido, look, it's-a like it was paved by angels.
ദധി, ബും ൭൦൦൨ ഠി ല്‍ നല.
I bet even the roads on the moon ain't this smooth.
ല്ധ്വല്ന്മന ഠി ധിബ്വാഥ 151 ടല്ദ്ദ ല്‍.
Doc, look at this!
൧൦൦, ന്യം
Shoulda tossed him into the cactus a lot sooner, huh?
ട്‌ സമ്സാണണ ഠി ഠി ഖ്ഖ്ഡട ലാ ഗയീ, 7
Well, he ain't finished yet. Still got a long way to go.
൧1 ലാല്ഥ്ന ടലിടട. [ഗീട്ുദധ് ഹാലുലി്മ്സുഒ.
Guido, look at Luigi!
ദധി, ബാധി!
This is fantastico!
[11111
That looks like fun! Mater, I got dibs, next turn!
പുംസ്ഥാഗനബുഥനറമ്ല്‍്‌ [ഗി്ല, ടവ മഠ നആിപലാടട ബി മയ്‌
Hey, Luigi, this new road makes your place look like a dump.
ധി, ടമിബാബബാധണിഭ്ം! ത്വ നന്വാമിധാധബി
That crazy old devil woman.
ഠ്‌ ഥംഭന്ഥ്ധന ഠ്യ
She's right!
ബബിത ഠി!
Guido!
ദധി
That punk actually did a good job.
8ധഠിമിധാലിമാല്്ബ 0ധക്ധിുതാദാ്ധട.
Well, now... where the heck is he?
ലാ ടല 111111:
Sheriff! Is he makin’ another run for it?
൧19 ലോദ ന്ലധിലി ൭?
No, no. He ran outta asphalt in the middle of the night,
1 ൧ ഭ്ഘാവ്ടക്ന ലയന ലാല നല്ണ 19൦,
and asked me if he could come down here.
൦൩ സ൭വദ്ധ ഠിദ 0ഠില ഠ്ഖ്് !ഭ ട്വ.
All he's tryin’ to do is make that there turn.
൧19 09 ഡാ ടലില്ര്വ്ധ ൭.
No, no, no, no! Oh, great.
൭൨൩,ഘാദ്്‌
Perfect turns on every track I've ever raced on.
൭ലില൭൨ ടബന്യാധന്൯ ഠി ടലില്വാ ൮ ല്വഥ്്ാമ.
Sheriff, why don't you go get yourself a quart of oil at Flo's.
ടല, 9 ൭9 ദ്ധവായി 0ല സ്സഖഗധിംത്ധ ഠി ക്ല ലം?
I'll keep an eye on him.
൧൮ ടി്ബ്വാല്മിത്ന ഠി.
Well, thanks, Doc. I've been feelin’ a quart low.
ലന മടി. എിവാഥന ൭൩ ല൭ടെ നആ്വട.
This ain't asphalt, son. This is dirt.
ബബ ധിത്വ ഹന്ധിയാബാവടടമം, വ ധന്വാധ.
Oh, great. What do you want? You here to gloat?
൧൧൭ ദ്ധ ലിറ ഉറു നമഗന്നലാട ഥി?
You don't have three-wheel brakes, so you got to pitch it hard,
1111-11-11: ധ്വഭന്൭ ലക സ്സ 0൪൦ലലില്ന്ന
break it loose and then just drive it with the throttle.
രാധ ഠന്വിയ്യി സ്സ
Give it too much, you'll be outta the dirt and into the tulips.
ലില്ധാസത്ം യവ നടടധിറിധസ്വഥലാണനടപാഥാദ ധി.
So you're a judge, a doctor and a racing expert.
ട്ഒഠി യ്ധഘിന്ന, ഠ9ഠ൨൦॥ ബാടിയ ധമ്പാദ.
I'll put it simple.
൧൮ ഠയ്വാ സ്ധഠ്ലി ട്വ.
If you're goin’ hard enough left, you'll find yourself turnin’ right.
ദ്രിദ്ധത്ധില്!ഭ ടലാലദ്വിനി, ധ്ധ ൭൭൫ നസ്പാലംലഭ ൭൬൫൭൨.
Right. That makes perfect sense. Turn right to go left! Yes! Thank you!
൭൨, ൭. 'ഗീണമാ നടടഥിലിയി വട ൭൩൭൦ ഥി! അച! ന്ന രട്്‌
Or should I say, "No, thank you"?
ഷ്്ധവാദ്ഡ്‌ ലവി, ലിന യടി ടല്ല്ല്ന്‌?
Because in Opposite World, maybe that really means, "Thank you"!
ലാലാ ഠിന ബ്ദ (ഹാലിം; ധാല്നലിത്ധം ന്നട്‌
Crazy grandpa car. What an idiot!
ലഘ് ഡഃറ്റിദ! 8ാം്വാദ്ധി!
Turn right to go left.
8ലിഠ്ലത്ഥ്ന ഥിലാ്യി ൩.
Guess what. I tried it.
വാദ ൭! ചവ 511 ബോ.
You know what? This crazy thing happened... I went right!
ഉ ലിയ ॥വാലില്വ, ട്വ ഹായി നബ
You keep talkin’ to yourself, people'll think you're crazy.
1ബിദബബാലലിയ്വാ ടബാ(്ന, ൦ 31൭൦0൧03 ത്വ 9॥ഒ.
- Thanks for the tip. - What? I wasn't talkin’ to you!
- ലിന മടി ഥന. -൧ിവ ധി ലാഘവ ഠുബിത്ധ!
- It looks great! This is great! - Ti piace, eh? Si, si, bellissimo.
പ്ുംസ്ഥാിഗലാട്‌!
Oh, Lord.
൨, സ്്ബി
Mater!
[ഴിമ്ല്‌
I need you to watch the prisoner tonight.
എിവവാലിധിത്ധുാബാധമ ന്ട്ണ ല്‍.
Well, dad-gum! Wait a minute. What if he tries to run again?
ഗണന യിദ്ധ ഠി ലോദി?
Just let him run outta gas and tow him on back.
ദല ഠി !ഭമ്ധ്ടന ടട, ധനി ഠി്വാലി॥
- But keep an eye on him. - Yes, sir!
- ലി ാലന്മിത്ഥ ഠിദ 11:11
While I'm stuck here paving this stinkin’ road,
ലട മിവ പാദ ലിമി ബ്‌...
Chick's in California schmoozing Dinoco.
ഠ്വ! ലബ്ബ സ്ഥാ ൧100 ൭1൮.
My Dinoco. Whoa, whoa, whoa! Who's touching me?
ടില്ാാഠ്ോ വ?
You have a slow leak. Guido, he fix.
1ദൃദ്ലിത്ധ 000 5൦. ദം മിയ്ബാടിദി.
You make-a such a nice new road.
!ദ്ധാധബുലി ബര്‍ സിം
You come to my shop. Luigi take-a good care of you.
ഉടാടനഭഭഠ്ല വ. ധി മ്മാ ത്വ ബാലി
Even though you not a Ferrari.
ലിദ്്വാഥനത്ധാധിക്ന ണ്ടി.
You buy four tires, I give you a full-a size spare
ദ്ധ! സ്വാദ്‌, ടവ ലി ഒ റുസികഥാല്ധനട!
- absolutely free! - Look, I get all my tires for free.
൧൮ ഠില്വാമ ട്വ ഒ മവ ഹാല്ധണട.
l like your style, eh?
1-11-11
You drive the hard bargain. OK. Luigi make you a new deal.
!ദ്ധ്വാഖബ്ല നല്ല. ധി വാഡ മഘാബ ബത.
You buy one tire, I give you three for free!
ദ്ധാല॥। ടബ്ബ വ, ടവ ലി 03 ല്ഡനട!
Would you look at that?
ോദത്ധ ഹാംലവ്ധ?
Ramone, Ramone!
ദനം! നം!
Then Luigi make you a new new deal.
ദ്രിദ്ധ ലാ ധിഠിവാധമഘമന ൭൮ ലാ10 0൧.
No, no, no, no. Deal me out. Pass. No, thank you.
1ലിലാല്ധിട. "ബ്ന യടി ട്വ.
- No, no, no, no. No. - This is it. My last offer.
ബബ ധന ട്വ ജന്ന
You buy one tire, I give you seven-a snow tires for free!
ദ്ധാല॥। ടബ്ബ വ, ട്വ ാലാത്ധ ്വധ്ന്മഖ ടി സ്വന!
Done. You interested, you call me. You know where I am.
(മിദ്ധധാല്സ്്‌, ടില്ഠ൦ ടവ. ദ്ധ ലസ ഠി നട്ട ടവ ാജഠ്.
Oh, Red, you missed a spot. See it right there?
ലാ, ടബ്൨ ന്വാദ്‌ടിവാണ്ടിന. പംസ്ഥാലി ട്ട?
- No! No! - On the hood right there.
൧ 95 ലാല്ഡ്ധ്വാ ബ്വ്നഡധ.
Stop, stop! That's cold!
ദലിഘലസ്‌! ടല്ഥിറി
Help! Please! Stop!
101൦! 1൮1൭൩ 8൦ന്‌!
Thanks, Red.
ലിനാ !൭ട॥0, ൦0
What was that for?
ഥി ല്വാദ?
- Do you want to stay at the Cozy Cone? - Huh?
ദ്ധ നല്ലാ 9 ഠ്യ ഠ്‌?
If you do, you gotta be clean.
പ്ഒഠി ന്ധ നട്ട വാട്ടി.
‘Cause even in hillbilly hell we have standards.
ടി ഠ। ന്ഥബ്[ബാനല്ഖണു, ദ്വി മഠ൭ ട്്0ഠ്ല.
What, I...? I don't get it.
എവ ല്വ്ല്നണന.
I thought I'd say thank you for doin' a great job.
ലാമി ധഘ്വോദന ലന ര൭ട॥൨ ടട വയാ
So I thought I'd let you stay with me. I mean, not with me!
൧വ നാ ന്മവാന്ലിത്ബിത്ധ ന്നാല്‍ ഠേ ടിവ,ധധിത്ന ണയി
But there. Not with me there, but there in your own cozy cone.
൧ ടാ. ദ്ധിത്ഥ 900 ലവ ഠി ട്ട, ദ്വ റിസിരബത്ധ ട്ടി.
- And I'd be in my cone, and it's... - Wait. Wait, you're being nice to me.
- ൧0 ടവ ഠ। ൭൩ ടിവി. -ര്രധവാധദ്ധാടിഗഥ്ണ ട്വ!
If you want to stay at the dirty impound, fine.
ദ്രിദ്ധിത്ധ ന്മ! ഠി യ്യാടന ല്ഘന്മ. ചവ നല.
- lunderstand you criminal types. - No, no, no, no. That's OK.
-[ര്രധബ്ട ഹബ്ബ്‌. - ഠി നന്യദ്വാമ.
- Yeah, the Cozy Cone. - It's newly refurbished.
- ഠഠജയ ഠെ - ലാ വാധബ്വാന്പാടിറ്ല്്‌.
Yeah, it's like a clever little twist.
19 ന൭൮൭ 0115
The motel's made out of caution cones, which, of course, cars try to avoid.
1ഴിഠലല്‍ ഠ്ലാ്ധമ ഠി ൭൨ ൮ ൭൭ ഡോദ ലല
But now we're gonna stay in them. That's funny.
ലയന ടിക 9 ഠി ഠ്ലി്മ്സഭ. 0.
Figure that all out on your own, did you?
ന്ധ ഠ്ല്വാദ നലല 0 ടാഗ്‌?
Cone number one, if you want.
10 ഗഠ്പാ ടബ്ബരിദ്ധിത്ധ ടിയ.
Hey, do I spy a little pinstriping tattoo back there?
ബ്ബ ടവ ന്യാ 1ട്വ്ല്ധ ഠി ലട്യ്ണ്ു ട്ട?
That's just a...
൮ ഡനട ടട്ഖ..
You saw that? Yeah. Just gonna be going.
ദ്ധ നലന്വാട്റ നം:
You know, I once knew this girl Doreen.
ഉല്ല മവ! ടം 99ഠ1ട, ൧൦൭൦൨.
Good-lookin' girl.
ണിം
Looked just like a Jaguar, only she was a truck!
പം സ്ഥാനേ വല, ദ്വി ടലാലാസ സ ലിറ
You know, I used to crash into her, just so I could spoke to her.
൧൮ ടല്ല്ധ ടല പാഠ ഠിദ ട്ധ്യാദൃര മിവലാഠില്വാലലിയ്വാ 990 ഠി.
- What are you talking about? - [don't know.
-൧്യാടിന്ധ ിയ്വാല്‌? - ന.
Hey, I know somethin’ we can do tonight, ‘cause I'm in charge of watchin’ you!
എവ ലസ ല്വാന്്വാഠില്വാധമ് നടി ബി ടലാലാ മവ ഠ്ഡ്ുടക്ന ന്മാ ത്ധ!
No, Mater, I gotta finish this road, and I have to get out of here.
100 ലയിഭ്ട ടില്ലിയ്ബുദി്ല ൭൭ മവ നട്ട്‌ ാല്യ! ഠ്0 ട്വ.
Well, that's all right, Mr. l Can't Turn On Dirt.
1ഒനലുല്വാമ, 50. ലിഗാ! ഷടട ധന്വാധ..
You probably couldn't handle it anyway.
ഗ്രന ത്വ 3 ണന്ഥാധമഠ്ലാ! ൧൧൩.
Whoa, whoa, easy now, Mater.
൨0-൫5.
You know who you're talkin’ to? This is Lightning McQueen.
ദ്ധ ലസ ടിന റാലിയ്വാ 9൩ ട്ല്വാദ? [ഠിട്ല്ഴിറ്വേംറ.
I can handle anything.
൧൮ നന്വാധനഠ്ല്വാ। ല്വാദ ട്വ.
- Mater, I'm not doin' this. - Oh, come on. You'll love it!
ചവ ിഗ്മിലി്ല്ഡിത്ന -കൃവിന ദ്ധ ല്ഖ്ലഡ്ല!
- Tractor-tippin's fun. - This is ridiculous.
- [ഗീലഠ131 ഥി 5൦൦0൦. - ൩ നന്റമ്ധ്‌.
All right, listen.
ഉല്ല ടി.
When I say go, we go. But don't let Frank catch you. Go!
8॥ വരദ ലി, 09 ലാല. ല്0൮൩0 ല്‌ ബിഘായ്വ. ൧0!
Whoa! Wait! Who's Frank?
കല്യാ ബറ
Mater!
[ഴിമ്ല്‌
Wait, Mater!
7ഥ്ാ9്ധ!
And they do the rest. Watch this.
1൭0 ന്ന്ഗ്ധട ടന. ഡാ ഇം.
l swear, tractors is so dumb!
ന്ധ, 70 നണട 0൦൦
I tell you what, buddy, it don't get much better than this.
ല്ലി യ, 191൮൬ 1ലാ1൨ ടലി ബ്‌.
Yep, you're livin' the dream, Mater boy.
ത്വ നന്നാ നല്ല] ഭ്വഠ്ധ്ാബബന്ധദ.
I don't care who you are, that's funny right there.
എവ ലിാലാധി। ത്വ ടില്ാമ. ്്ധഖ.
Oh, your turn, bud.
ല്ി്ബത്ധ.
Mater, I can't. I don't even have a horn.
1ടിധാഠില്‍, 'ഗീട്ല. എവ ലിഗമഠ്ദ ബലാഥ.
- Baby. - I'm not a baby.
- 8. -൧ിവ ധിത്വ ഒ.
Fine. Stop! Stop, OK? All right. I'll do something.
8:10. 3ലാലസ്‌! 81961, ടവ ടിഷ്ബാധമ്‌ ടടട്വദ്ധി!
That's Frank.
ബിം.
Run!
[8-1
Here he comes, look out!
൮ ഠി ഠാ! വ!
Run! He's gonna get ya!
1൭0! ൧ ലിത്ഥ ഠ്ല്ലാസിത്ധ!
Customers!
ലലാ
No, no, no.
11 ലില്ലി
Tomorrow night we can go look for the ghostlight!
[ഗിഠണ ടട 0൦16൨ ദേ സ്ഥ ന്മന്ധ!
- l can't wait, Mater. - Oh, yeah, I'm tellin’ ya!
-൧ിവ 11 ലാല - 8ല്ധി മവ ്യ്വാ!
Oh, boy, you gotta admit that was fun!
ദ്ധ നട്ട്‌ നലുദിവ, 19ഠി മന നബുനറമ്ല്‍്‌
Oh, yeah... yeah.
൦൮൭.
Well, we better get you back to the impound lot.
ദചിധന്മ നല ത്ധ ഭഖ്ധാടന ല്ല.
You know, actually, Sally's gonna let me stay at the motel.
ലാലല, ടലിലാലന്ലിത് ട്വ 1009 9 നല.
- Gettin’ cozy at the Cone, is we? - Oh, come... No. No, are you kidding?
-പ്ദ്ധാല്ടലടട ഠ। ൩൭? - ലാലി. യ്ധാല്യ്ല്്ധ?
Besides, she can't stand me. And I don't like her, to be honest.
൧19 1ട51വല്ഘ്ലാല്ബാി ലിവ ഉ ലിവ 5 ധിതിത്ഥ ഠഒ.
Yeah, you probably right. Hey, look, there's Miss Sally!
ഗ്രന ബി ത്മത്വ. ധാഥ ലല്‌
Where, where?
൧ നന്മ?
- You're in love with Miss Sally. - No, I'm not.
-ര്ര്ധ ഠ്ട്വ്യമ്ധ ണ്മ 00 ലിലി - 11991൦
- Yes, you do. - No way.
ത്വയി ഗ്ന്ട. - ലസ്ഥാിനന.
- Way. - Come on, look...
ഗ്ധ്ി1൩൬൩.
- You're in love with Miss Sally! - Real mature.
-ര്ര്ധവദ്ധ ഗ്ന ൦ ഠി - ദ്ധ നണമ്യ നട്ട, ഗല.
- You love her. You love her. - Wait...
ദ്ധ വ്ലിത്ഥ ദ. ്ധ എസ്മ ഠി!
You love her! You love her. You love her.
ദ്ധ വസ്മലിത്ഥ ഠ1ഒ. ദ്ധ ബ്ലിത്ഥ ഠദിദ്ധ ഗ്ന്മ്ിക്ന ഠി!
All right. OK. Mater, enough!
8ം॥റ൩ഗിട്ല, ഡിഡ്വാ!
- Will you stop that? - Stop what?
- 8ംില്വിത്ധ സിത്ന? - ഷ്യ?
Driving backwards. It's creeping me out. You're gonna wreck.
ഴിണമാധ ഭ ലഖു. 'ദീണ്മ്ഡിക്ന ടവ. ദ്ധ ടിയബാലിബാഠ നബ.
Wreck? Shoot! I'm the world's best backwards driver!
[്ഠാല്‌? 1919൩ ഷവ ഗന്ധ ലാലലാ ണി ലവി!
You just watch this right here, lover boy.
ധോദത്ധ ൭൦൦
What are you doing? Watch out! Look out!
൧൧൭ ദ്ധാധമ? 50-5൩!
Mater? Mater!
ഗിമ്ല ഗ്ല!
Hey, take it easy, Mater!
ധാ നലല, [ഥല്‌
He's nuts.
൧19 951913
No need to watch where I'm goin’.
1ലിലാല്ധ ഇ ഭര ന്ന ടവ 0൭.
Just need to know where I've been.
ഡ്ധണടഡ ഠി നന്മ ദവ ഠ്ല്വാബ്യ്‌.
Whoa, that was incredible! How'd you do that?
ധാധ്‌ നന്ബിറുധാത്ല്‍്‌ ാറുല്നാന്മ ദ്ധാധബ്ാട്്ഡ?
Rearview mirrors. We'll get you some, and I'll teach you if you want.
ന്ന നന്പാവാലലിയ്ാ. പ്ൂംസ നമ 0൦॥ ഠ്വ മിത്ഥ ല്യ്ലത്ധ.
Yeah, maybe I'll use it in my big race.
ഗ്ധ്ിന്൬൩ ല്വവാംലവറ്റന്മ ിന്വാലിധസ്ാദ്ബലാട്ല ലിവ.
What's so important about this race of yours, anyway?
൧൧൭൮൭ 0 ടബ്‌ 1ല്മാ ാലിധ്ാ് ബ്‌?
It's not just a race. We're talking about the Piston Cup!
ദധി ടല ഹാലിധ്സാണ. ല്ല ലിപി 015൧0.
I've been dreaming about it my whole life!
ചവ ന്ന്ഥ॥ിത്ഥ ന്മ ടല്ഥ് വ്ഠ്ധോ ദയ്‌
I'll be the first rookie in history ever to win it.
൧൮ ടിയു ല്ലാ ഠി ഠ്ഥ്ി൭ നണട.
And when I do, we're talkin’ big new sponsor,
ഉട ടവ നട്ടു, ല്നലിന്മ്രാലല്യദ ബനു ടല,
with private helicopters.
9൩ ൯൦॥000ല ാബ്ബാദഠി.
No more medicated bumper ointment. No more rusty old cars.
151 സ്സദ്വാബിാദ്‌ ഭലം ഡവാലിത്വ്‌.
What's wrong with rusty old cars?
(രന്ല്വാ ധി ൩൭ ഡാലിയ
Well, I don't mean you, Mater. l mean other old cars. You know?
ചവ (ലഗനല്ഴ്ധഠിയ്വത്ധ, [ഗ്ഖ്ല്‌. ഗീഭ്ധഠ മിഡി ഡം 1൭0.
- Not like you. I like you. - It's OK, buddy.
- ധി നാണ യ്ധ. ലവ ടധിയിത് ത്വ. - ടണലും, യ്യ.
Hey, you think maybe one day I can get a ride in one of them helicopters?
ദ്ധ ടാ ടദ്ധഡിഘി നമസ ടവ 0ഠ൦ില ഡന്പവാ ലിഗോ?
I mean, I've always wanted to ride in one of them fancy helicopters.
ഉ ഠ്ധ്ധ ല്വന്ഞാണന ന॥00ല॥00ല ന്മ ഥലപ്ബ.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, sure, sure. - You mean it?
യ, 0൧01ല്‍. -ര്രധ നലിത്ധാി്സുത്‌?
Oh, yeah. Anything you say.
൭. ൧൭ ടല്യന്ധ യമ.
I knew it. l knowed l made a good choice!
൧൮ ഠ്ല മാല എവ ല്ഡ ഠ്ല്വാധദ്ലമ്സര ലിറ
In what?
ല്വ॥ന്ഥ ല്വാദ?
My best friend.
ദ്ധബിത്ഥാ ലിവ.
See you tomorrow, buddy!
പ്ധന്വാദ ര്ധ ടംപിയധബ്‌
McQueen and Sally parked beneath a tree,
0ഗഥേധടെ റ്റെ ൭9 വ്‌ ൧ഒഗഒ൭0 ടലാഠ7ഠഥ ൧07൭..
K-i-s-somethin'-somethin-somethin’-t!
..ഒറ്ററ ൧ലഥ്ാഥ്ഥ!
Number one. Number one... Number one!
പുഠ്ധം ടദ്ധ! ൮൭, ന്പാം ടമ്ധ!
- This is nice. - Hey, Stickers.
നി മേസിം - ല്‍, ൧ലില്വ്ച്‌!
- I'm sorry. - You scared me. You gotta be careful.
-ഗീടലിയ്ഥ മിവ - [ദ്ധ ടിഡി മിവ.
I scared myself . . scaring you scaring me.
ചവ ടലി ധന ല്ഡ്‌ 1ലിഭ്യഥിത്തിത്ധ.
- [ mean, I wasn't like "scared" scared. - No, of course not. No.
-ഗീടിദ്ധഠി മിവവാധിത്ബ്ട മിയ ധാബി. -ല്വ ടലയ!। ഠി
- l was more... - loverheard you talkin’ to Mater.
൧൮ ഠബുലത്ധവാലലിയ്വാ ഠ്റ്ബ്ഴിദ്ല.
When? Just now? What, what did, what did you hear?
1901 ചാട ന്ധ ഠ്യ?
Something about a helicopter ride.
ടടധദ്ഡ ന്നു സന്ധാാ ല॥ര്വമ്ല..
Oh, yeah. Yeah, he got a kick out of that, didn't he?
൭, ഠി ടലഠ0൦0ഠഹുബിഠ്ടെ പ, ന?
- Did you mean it? - What?
-ര്രധ നലിത്ധാി്സുത്‌? - ഷ്യ?
- That you'll get him a ride. - Who knows?
പന്ധിത ദ
First things first. l gotta get outta here and make the race.
ണാ സ്വഃ ദ്ധ. ചവ നട്ട യി ലി ടബ്‌ ഠ്‌ ട്വാ! ഭരാല്ധമ്പാദല.
You know... Mater trusts you.
ദ്ധ ല്ഡ,്‌ഴിട്ലാല്മയിക്ിത്ഖ.
Yeah, OK.
൭, 911.
- Did you mean that? - What?
-[ര്രധ നലിത്ധാിത്ബ്ധ? - ഷ്യ?
Was it just a "Yeah, OK", or "Yeah... OK" or "Yeah, o-OK"?
൧൭1൭൨ ബ,ാട॥ഠി0 ടമ്പാ॥ മ ട്വ ട്വ നണ്ണി.
Look, I'm exhausted. It's kinda been a long day.
൧വഭ്വാലമ്മല. 160 ടാ ന്ലി ബ.
Yeah, OK. G'night.
൭, 911. ലന ന1ഒണ.
Hey, thank you.
0, (ലിന ട്ട.
What did you just say?
൧൧൭ ദ്ധാിത്൭?
You know, thanks for lettin' me stay here.
ലന മടിനക്ഷന്മ ല്മ്വിത്വ ലിവ ലാല്‍ 9 ട്ബ്‌.
It's nice to be out of the impound, and this is... It's great.
൭ല൦0൦01ല്യാമക്ധല ഠി യധാടന ല്ഘന്ഥ ഠ്൩1൪൩ബ ലാട.
- Newly refurbished, right? - Yeah.
- 8 ലിന്‌? - ൭.
- G'night. - Good night.
- ൭ലണമ നാണ.
Will you turn that disrespectful junk off?
8ഠില ലല്‌ നട്ബാബാ്ടാധസിബ ലന
Respect the classics, man. It's Hendrix!
ലഠന്നട്‌ ട॥ന ടബ !ഠി9ട॥൦ ബ്ന
I gotta get outta here!
൧൮ നട്ട്‌ ാല്യ! ദ ടല!
Hey, have you seen the Sheriff? Oh! Oh, my gosh.
ദ്ധ ഠി ന്ന ചണ
- Hey, what are you doin’? - Get a good peek, city boy?
- ്യാടിന്ധാധമ്റ -ഗീല്റിസ്മി, വറഖ?
I just need my daily gas ration from the Sheriff.
൧൮ ന്മധലയ്വ്ന ന്സ്വവഘിക്ന മവ ഠ്ലി ടഘ്‌.
Wait for him at Flo's. Get outta here.
ലലറ്ി ദ ഭഠ്ല 6൦. ലിയാ ലയി ഠ്ലി ടബ്‌.
I've been trying to get outta here for three days!
ഉന്ന ടവ ബോടാല്യ]ി ഠ്ലി ട്ബ്‌!
Hope you enjoyed the show!
1-11-11 ടലഠാവല്യഠവാഭന്പാല്മ്ല്‍്‌
Whoa, Doc.
പുലി വധ, ൧0൦0൦.
Time to clean out the garage, buddy, come on.
[ഗീടാ ധിരന റവ, ലല.
He has a Piston Cup?
൧19 ൭ ലിലി ലിട്ന്‌?
Oh, my gosh.
എനി
Three Piston Cups?
നറു ലല ല്ട്ഥന?
You have three Piston Cups. How could you have...
ദ്ധ ഠി 13 ലിലി 015൧൨.
Il knew you couldn't drive. I didn't know you couldn't read.
ചവ ല്ഡാത്ധലം്ധി നടനമ്ഥര്‍്ധ, ട്വ ല്സിത്ധ ലിലി നബസ്ബാദേ.
- You're the Hudson Hornet! - Wait at Flo's, like I told ya!
-ര്രധിട0റ്ധാ്ടംംണല്‌ - നാ ഠി ഭാ 0൦!
Of course. I can't believe I didn't see it before.
ചവ മലാല 151നലന്വാ ടലാല്ഥ്ന ബ്‌.
You're The Fabulous Hudson Hornet!
!ദ്ധില്വ്ധര്‍്ടംബ്ംന ലാട്വ്ധി
You used to hold the record for most wins in a season. Oh, we gotta talk.
ചാ മിധരണന്മന്യക ഠ്ന ട്വ സ്വട്ന.
- You gotta show me your tricks. Please. - [ tried that.
- രവ നടട॥ി ല്ല ലിവ ഭ്വാലഖ്ധ്ബിത്ഖ. - ൧൮ ൭11 ഡീ.
You won three times! Look at those trophies!
1099 ഭ്യ്ന്ന്‌ 1ന്യിടദ-ലിലിട്ധ!
You look. All l see is a bunch of empty cups.
ദ്ധ ഈം ചാട൮൬൭ മവ നന്വാ% 131ല ഡബരടംു.
You know, some automotive yoga could really lower your RPM's, man.
3 0ഠ1ല ബിാിത്ലയന്മ്ിത്ഖ.
Oh, take a car wash, hippie.
ലി ഥല്്പ്ധട.
Yeah, look at my husband, y'all! That's your color!
ന്യ ദ്ധി മവ൮, ടണ്ഡട! വ ഡഘന്മത്ധ!
- Yellow, baby. - You smokin’ hot!
ധ്രു, ടന. - ദ്ധ ട്ട ടല!
There he is.
ധ്യാഥ ഠി
Oh, my gosh! Did you know Doc is a famous racecar?
ദ്രസ്ധ ടന്ധദ ്ഡ ൧ഉഠഠഷ്ദദധസ്പാു ലിഭന്ല്‌?
- Doc? Our Doc? - Not Doc Hudson.
൧൦? ൧ഠധിയ്മ്പ്‌?
No, no, no, no, it's true! He's a real racing legend.
5 211:1 6 :11111:11:16-1-1
He's The Fabulous Hudson Hornet!
൧19 10ഠട൦0 11൦ന6൮൭ 0ലാട്‌!
Fabulous? I never seen Doc drive more than 20 miles an hour.
൧൮ മലാല ാംഗഥംം ഗനഠ്ധിലാ1ഠ്ച 20 ബ്ബ ടല്ണ.
I mean, have you ever seen him race?
!ദ്ധവാണ31 ഠി വാലിധസാമ?
No, but I wish I could have. They say he was amazing!
1ഠിപ്ല്യ വിദ്ധി ലാഖ്‌. [ഗി0ിലയത്ം ഠി നല്മ്റുധാത്ല്‍്‌
- He won three Piston Cups! - He did what in his cup?
- ൧9 നല ലപ്[ദ ലിട്ഥബ്‌ - ൧9 0൮൭ ല്വാദ ഠി ഖല ഠി?
I think the heat's startin’ to get to the boy!
ഭ്യാമ്മടണ 5100൮൭ ഠി ഭ്‌
Well, I'll say! Look how red he is.
ഴിണഘാലാദ്ധി! 1ല്ഠു൦വാല്ല്വാദ നല്ല യന്ന ഠഒ.
Yeah, I think he needs a new coat of poly, man.
൧1 ലാലിധിത്ന ടബ്ബല്യി്ടബാഠ നല.
- Are you sick, buddy? - You are lookin’ peaked.
-[ര്ര്ധ ടിന - രര ന്ഥാലിലാധഠമ
He needs a new coat of poly for sure!
൧1൭ നണട ഹല്ധിത്ഥ ഹ നല്‌
Hey, hey! What are you doin'?
൧൧൭ ദ്ധാാധ?
It's OK, Sheriff. You can trust me, right?
ദ്ധാഠില്വ്വായമുര 09 1൨, ത്ന?
I trust you, all right. It's him I'm worried about.
എവവാമയരിയ്ല ത്വ. ൧1൮൭ ലിവ റ്ട്ധിത്വ.
I trust him.
൧വവാഹമയിയ്വ ഒ.
- Come on, let's take a drive. - Adrive?
- കൃവിവ്വാണ്യ! നണട. -ഗീനണമറഠ്ധ?
Yeah, a drive.
ഴീണമനാധ.
Don't you big city racecars ever just take a drive?
ദ്രന്ധ ഭഘ്ടധ്ബാാഖ്മ്ല 1ടിലാണട ൩൭൧൭! നനണമ്്ധ?
No. No, we don't.
1ഠിയ്മ്ി വാല്മി
Hey, Stickers! You comin’ or what?
ല്‍, ലല്ല യവ ന്ലഥാഖ്യ! ടി
- And you thought he was gonna run. - Hey, can you believe it, man?
ഉത്ധ 7 ദ ലിഖ്ബി്ധിത്ഥ 0.
He actually thought Doc was a famous racecar!
8ഠില്നത്ധലാലമയ ഠി 004 ൧൦൦ നന ഘട ലിഭന്ല്‌?
That's so too much!
[ഴില്ലന്വാമ്ധ!
OK, you got me out here. Where are we goin'?
ദ്ധ ഠ്ല്വാലുദ്ാദ് മഡിര്ധല. ഗ്മ നലഭ നന്മ?
I don't know.
എവ ലിവല്ഡ.
Wow. What is this place?
൧സ്ബാഠ। 1്വാദ്‌ല്വാ ബ്‌?
Wheel Well.
ഗല ഗല.
Used to be the most popular stop on the mother road.
ഉല്ല സ്ഥാനി 0102 ലിഭന്ലി 10 ധന.
This place?
1ല്വാദ്‌ബ്‌?
Yeah, imagine.
ദിയ
Oh, imagine what it must have been like to stay here.
മചൃാബബാമാല്നട്മു രാമസ ഘാ! ഠി ട്ബി.
You know, I don't get you.
എവ ല്വ്ല്നണന.
How does a Porsche wind up in a place like this?
ഗീഠണാന ൧ 0ഠില ടന്വാട! ൫ ന്ഥി?
Well, it's really pretty simple. I was...
ഗ്വാ ട്വ. ഥി 31൮...
.an attorney in LA livin' life in the fast lane, and...
.ാഠ്റേണ ഠി, വിഠ്ധ്വാ ഠിന ദ്ധബ്ദ ടട ടി.
Oh, you were, were you? Were you rich?
൨൭? ദ്ധിത്ൃ?
- What? - Just... clues to the puzzle.
റ്ധണ്ടാബ്ധബ്ഥിധം ടാഡ ടയല
Yeah, OK. Well, that was my life.
൭, 911. ധില് ബ്ലാ ടവ.
And you know what?
ഉബത്ധ സ ല്ലാ?
It never felt... happy.
19 മലാല മട സാ.
Yeah. I mean... really?
൭. ഴിലിത്ധം വ, ദൃ?
Yeah. So I left California.
പ്9ഠി ടവ ന്ന്യാലിക്ന 041.
Just drove and drove and finally broke down right here.
ഴീണാധ ന്യാ ടലി ടിബി.
Doc fixed me up, Flo took me in.
ഉഠലാദിറി ൮. ൦ ഡന്ധഥബ്യിയ്ഥ ലവ.
Well, they all did. And I never left.
170: ട്ധ്ഓ3 ലവ. ൧൭0 ടവ 1ടിലാലനടന്ന്യാലിയ്ന ണ്ട്‌ ല്‍.
Yeah. You know, I understand.
൧വ്ല്മ്ണ.
You need a little R and R. Recharge the old batteries.
!ദ്ധവാലിധാലലില്‌. ടട ടണ്ഡ്ദ ഖലീ.
But you know, after a while, why didn't you go back?
ല്ലാ ടലിലാടട വ, ല്വാദ്ധ ഥാന
I fell in love.
എചഡൃങ്ബറ ഗ്ന.
Yep.
ഒ.
- Corvette? - No.
- (൭൫൦ ഠംസങ്ല? - ധി.
fell in love with this.
൧ഡൃണ്ഡറ ഗ്ന്ട 90 ബ.
Whoa. Look at that.
ധോദ ംഗ്ബ.
Look, they're drivin’ right by.
[ഗി നലിന്മട ദല.
They don't even know what they're missing!
[ഗി0ിലിവല്ഡ ലാവ ലിലാദട!
Well, it didn't used to be that way.
ഉധിധാധിയ്ാല്റ്വ.
Yeah. Forty years ago, that Interstate down there didn't exist.
5ന്ഥബ്വാധിഥ നല ല്ലം നട്ട ലിഗ്വ്ധാഠി.
Really?
ദത?
Yeah. Back then,
ഉധിധ,
cars came across the country a whole different way.
ഭ്൭്മല്ധ 900 9 1൭൧.
How do you mean?
൧൧൭ നലിത്ധാ ന്ധ?
The road didn't cut through the land like that Interstate.
ട്ടി ലാഹി നടന ലാധ്ന്മര സ്ഭ.
It moved with the land, you know? It rose, it fell, it curved.
ാുല്ല്ലിയ്മ്മി. പ്ലിധാധിറ്‌, ഡബ്ബവാധിന, നലസിാല।.
- Mornin’! - Nice day, huh?
- ടല ണമ ഥഠാ!! 00൭ ന്ന?
Cars didn't drive on it to make great time.
ദ്വല്ദ്വാധിക്ന നനട്ഥഠ്ധ മട 110 ടലന്വാദ! ലോ.
They drove on it to have a great time.
ഗറില മ്മ 1॥ധാല്ടലഠനാ
Well, what happened?
൧൧൭൮൭ ലിവ?
The town got bypassed just to save ten minutes of driving.
ദം ബി 1ഠിഗി॥ല്ധി ൭൮ ലാലാ നല്ക 10 സ്ബ്‌നടട ലാല്ല.
How great would it have been to see this place in its heyday!
1ല്വ ലാട നല നണ്ണി ടല്നമടടാ മാനദ ഭൃുബിാ്സ!
I can't tell you how many times I've dreamed of that.
1ലിവാഠില്‍ന്ല്ലത്ട ല്ഘ്വാഘല്വാമവാന്ഥിത്ന ബബ.
But one of these days we'll find a way to get it back on the map.
ല്ലി ടബ്ബ നല ണ്‌ ന ലിഖ്ബധന്ഥാമ 190 ഥിഭ്ബാലി॥ക് സ്ഥല ടര ഠ്വ
Yeah. Hey, listen, thanks for the drive.
ലന മടി നണമാധ ട്ടാ നി ല്‍.
l had a great time.
൧വ മന ട൦൦0൦.
It's kinda nice to slow down every once in a while.
൭ല൦001ലാ0ഠ്ധവാലില്മ് ടല ടലയഒ.
You're welcome.
ലന മടി ്വാഃ॥.
Hey, listen, listen!
ഉലാ
If anybody asks you, we was out smashin' mailboxes, OK?
ദ്രിദ്ധ ഇ ബസ, ൯90൮ സ്വടന്മ്വ്്ലിര്ട ധ്യ!
Oh, man, the paint's still wet!
൭ നാട്ിവാടടമ്വ്‌
No, no, no, no! Get out of the store!
(്വ്ധല ഠ്ലി ഭാ!
Hey! Don't eat the radial! Here, take-a the snow tires.
൭൦ നലക ഖല്ധി എസ്പാ॥ ഒര്വ 591.
- Mater! - wasn't tractor-tippin'!
-ഗീമ്ലി! -൧ിവ മലായ! 'ന॥॥0ക് അിറ്ം്‌
Then where did all these gol-durn tractors come from?
പഠി ഠ്ലി നന്മ സിടണ്ഡട ക്ട?
- Whoa, boy! - Hey! Hey, guys!
പ, ടലന്ധല
There's one goin’ this way.
ദ്ധ മിറ നന്മ ഭ ട്വ.
I got it.
ചവ ധബടിത്ന ഠിഒ.
Come here, little tractor, come here.
[മീലി ട്ര, ലിറ ഭി.
Yeah, that's a good tractor.
വ അിറ്ംര്‍ ല॥
No, no, no, no, come here.
ഴി ട്വ.
You're not supposed to go wandering off all...
ദ്ധ ലിഥാണ്ഡിത്ധല നല്യത്ഡ..
.-alone.
..ടാ(്ന
What are you doin' with those old racin' tires?
൧൧൭ ദ്ധാാധമ നമു 1111111111
Come on, Doc, drive.
ഷുഡ്‌, ൧൦൦. ൧0൨.
Wow.
൧സ്ബാഠ।
You're amazing!
ദ്ധ നല്മ്ദുധാത്ല്‍്‌
What are you doin'?
൧൧൭ ദ്ധാാധ?
Doc, wait!
൧൦൦, ഡ്റഠ്ധ!
Giddup right in there! Come on, Rusty.
ഷുഡ്‌ ലാട, ഡട്ലി
Doc, hold it! Seriously, your driving's incredible!
ബഖി, ഗണമ്റഠ്ധ്ിത്ധ ലാണ്‌
- Wonderful. Now, go away. - Hey, mean it. You've still got it!
- ളമറ്റട. ടലഷ്വണ 0൭യ. -[ര്ര്ധ നടി ഹാലി!
- I'm askin’ you to leave. - Come on.
11-11-11]:
I'm a racecar, you're a much older racecar,
1 :1111-1 ദ്ധദധ്നിലാബം
but under the hood you and I are the same.
ദ്വ ടലാലസ്൭ ൭ ടണട ടദ്വദ.
We are not the same! Understand? Now, get out.
ന് 151: ടാ! ടലിയ്വ്ാ യി.
How could a car like you quit at the top of your game?
ഗീ യ്വ 0ഠ1ല1 ലീല ടല്നടടപാലമാ്ട ഠി വാധ്വ
You think I quit?
ദ്ധ 003 മ്ഡാണ്സി?
Right.
രര.
Your big wreck in '54.
(ഭനദബാബാടടല ദ്ധവാദഠ്ദ ന്ഥ 54.
They quit on me.
ഗിയ ാധ്പട ഒട ൩0 ലിവ.
When I finally got put together, l went back expecting a big welcome.
8॥ഃ വ ഠ്ഖ്വാധി. മ്വ്ാഃ॥ നലാന്മജ്വിനയ്ഥ ലിന്റ നലിദ.
You know what they said? "You're history."
ച്ഡ ല്വാ്സിലിത്ട? ദ്ധ ഠ്ല്വുദഠി ടല.
Moved right on to the next rookie standing in line.
[ഗി0ഠ്ലി ലിന ഥാല്്ിക്ന 090 ലാല്ഥസ്ാ ലാസ.
There was a lot left in me.
ഗീാട്വാബുഖ:ടണമ്റട്‌ ന ന ടവ.
I never got a chance to show 'em.
എവ ഡന്ന ൭0മഠ്ദ ഹല്ധബാ ന൭1൦ഡബ്ഥിറക്്വാദഠ്ദ നിം
l keep that to remind me never to go back.
എവ ടന്ന, ധിാഖ്ത്ന ടിവ ട്ധ്യാദൃര്നാബാഃ॥ഗദണ്ഡിദ.
I just never expected that that world would...
ചവ ഡന് ടാ ദ്ര
.. would find me here.
ടിര്ബധ്വാ ടവ ഠ।ട്ബ്‌.
- Hey, look, Doc, I'm not them. - Oh, yeah?
“൧0൦, ടിധാധിയ്ന ന്നി. ബ്ര?
No, I'm not.
ധിന്വ
When is the last time you cared about something except yourself, hot rod?
8॥ ന്ധ ന്ധി ാടഠ്ധി॥ത്ഥ ല്യം ൭0 ടല ഠി ഠ്0ിത്ധ?
You name me one time and I will take it all back.
ഡയ്ിക് ടാഡ ത.. ൦൩ വ മടിക് ലിടന്ഡിട യ്ത ലിവ.
I didn't think so.
11-11-15
These are good folk around here, who care about one another.
170: ടസ്ധാവാടിി ട്ലി, ടന ബാ ൧0൭ ലന്മട ടാഡ ടണട 1൭0൧.
I don't want 'em depending on someone they can't count on.
എവ ലിഗന്ല്ലാല്മജ്വാ 090൭ ൦൮൭ 1൭1൦ല൨ ഠിന്ല്ഭ്വാിത്ന.
Oh, like you? You've been here how long
ഗണ ധ്ധ?
and your friends don't even know who you are?
ദ്ധബിയ്ഥിത്ഖ 1ടിലഭ്ഹലി ധന ടില്ാഠ ഠി ത്വ.
Who's caring about only himself?
ടില്വാ൮൬൭ നസഭ൭ാടറ്ധി॥ത്വ സ്ഥാ ഠന്സഭ?
Just finish that road and get outta here!
ടില്യിയ്്ട്ണ ഠ്ബബാലമ്ബ്വട ദക ടല!
Will you turn that disrespectful junk off?
൭൩ നല്ലാ ധിയാ!
Respect the classics, man.
ല൦ന്ന്ി ടബബി !ഠി9ട॥
He's done.
൧19 1 ട്വ.
He must've finished it while we was all sleepin’.
ല്വ ഠിഃ ട്ല്വിഖ്വ ടല്നടട ൯9 ടലി 1.
Good riddance.
ദലിഘസ്പ്ധടിട.
He's gone?
൧19 9510 ല്യി?
Well, we wouldn't want him to miss that race of his.
ദൃതില്പന്ട ലിഗന്ലിദ ശ്വഘാഠ1ബാല്ധമ്പാദ.
- Oh, dude, are you crying? - No! I'm happy!
-!ര്രധ നടന്മഘട? - 1൦ മിവ!
I don't have to watch him every second of the day anymore!
എവ ലിഥാഠ്ധ 1995 ഠി ടഖില്വ ടാണിയ!!
I'm glad he's gone!
ചവ സ്ഭ ഠദ ഠ്ദ്വ്ാല്യി!!
What's wrong with Red?
(രന്ല്വാട ൦൦൦൦?
Oh, he's just sad ‘cause you left town
൧19 ധന ട൦ഠ10൩ ടലാദ്ധ ദ്ധ ാലിത്ഥ ദ്ദ
and went to your big race to win
ഠബബ്വാ! 'ഭാല്ധമ്പാദമ്ന റാടടല്ലിത്ധഖ
the Piston Cup that you've always dreamed about your whole life
10നണടലമ! ല്ലി ലട ഴു ത്വ ന്ഥി ടല്ഥ്ബി ബ്ലോത്ധ
and get that big ol’ sponsor and that fancy helicopter you was talkin' about.
൦ ഠ്ദ്ാമ ഹാല്യ്യമ്വാടട ദ്ര ൫ല॥000ല ലാട യ്വ യ്യാ.
Wait a minute!
പ്ുംസി ഠ്ധ്ധ!
I knowed you wouldn't leave without saying goodbye.
എവ ല്ധധിത്ധ ലിത്ബാഖ്യ! 1ല്വാദ ധ്ലോ ടലദണ 09.
What are you doin' here? You're gonna miss your race.
ദ്ധ ടിക്ിഷ്ഘാഠിഥലിധ്സാ്ിത്ഖ.
Don't worry. I'll give you a police escort, and we'll make up time.
൧൮ ടിയ്ബാധണാന്നാണാം॥ട ട്ധ്വാദയ൭ ലോങ്‌ ടദന്വാല.
Thank you, Sheriff.
ലിനാ !൭ട॥0, ടന്‌.
But you know I can't go just yet.
ല്ലാ മഡാലധന്പാഠില്വയാല്യി.
Well, why not?
(രന്ല്വാ 1ഠിറ്‌
I'm not sure these tires can get me all the way to California.
ചവ ലിലി ഖല 0ഠില ഡെ മിവ ഭ ലി.
Yeah, does anybody know what time Luigi's opens?
൧൧൭ ടലടില്യാ ല്ഡ 019 1൭ഠ് 119 ഡിയു?
Grazie, Mr. Lightning. Grazie!
ലന മടി!
- Would you look at that! - Our first real customer in years!
വാദ ൦1
lam filled with tears of ecstasy,
എവ ഠ്രാ്ഡ്ല്‍ ൦0 ബഘിടബിഭടയ(യന,
for this is the most glorious day of my life!
ധി വയ ലാട്നാവാഖ്മാ1 ഠിണവഠ്ധാ ലിവ്‌
All right, Luigi, give me the best set of blackwalls you've got.
80, ൨91. 3ലിത് ടവ ട്വ ട൦ഘ ദിഷ വരു റാലി
You don't-a know what you want. Luigi know what you want.
ഠി ദ്ധ ലിവല്ഡ ലാഭ ത്ധ നട്സ. ധി ലസ ല്വായ ത്വ ന്മ്ഡ.
Blackwall tires. They blend into the pavement.
1ദുഖ്വ ലിജി ടന ഡാ ബട.
But-a this...
ല്ല ബി...
Whitewall tires!
ദുഖ ഗന്ധ!!!
They say, "Look at me! Here I am! Love me."
ഗ്0ിലയം, ണു ലിഡ്‌ ചവ ഠി ടല! ദയാ ല്ഡ്‌്‌
All right, you're the expert.
ദ്ധ ലാട.
Oh, and don't forget the spare.
ഉംബ്യന്പ്ധാദ ഒ സ്ദ.
- Perfetto. Guido! - Peet stop!
ലന്യാധന്നു, ബിഠ്ം!
What did Luigi tell you?
൧൧൭ ൨൨19 ൧്ട്ഡത്ധ?
Wow, you were right. Better than a Ferrari, huh?
ബഖി ത്മത്വ. 1ലാവാലിറ്ലി ണ്ട്ഥിദത്‌?
It's a conspiracy, man!
9 ട്ധിരട്ര്്ടി!
The oil companies got a grip on the government!
ഖൃ്ധിര സുഖദ! ഭജ.
They're feedin' us a bunch of lies, man.
[ഗീിലാംഘനു ടദ്യദ 09 019.
OK, I'll take a case.
819911, ലിവ ്ബാ॥ ടമ്ധാല്യട.
Yeah.
ഒ.
Ka-chow.
ലാട!
- Here she comes! - Places, everybody. Hurry!
-[ധ്വാഥ ഠി ക്യാ! - ല്ധപാലമാ്ട ഠി ്വാമ നാട്ന-ന്ടട്.
Act natural.
8ലിമമഗനണ 01953.
- Hi, Sally. - Buon giorno!
ലം! ടി
All right, what's goin' on?
ഭം, ലാവ ലിവ?
Ladies and gentlecars,
ദ്ധ-ഡണണ ക ല്ധാധണ,
please welcome the new Lightning McQueen!
നല്വാല്ടി ലക ധിദിംറ്ധംബുര്‍ ദ്ധി
What do you think?
൧൭ ദ്ധ നിന
Radiator Springs looks pretty good on me.
ടി ഠി വ ലിവ ഭനമ്ബിലാവാദ്വട.
I'll say.
ചവ ടല്ഡ്വ്ധ
Ka-chow.
ലാട!
You're gonna fit right in in California.
ദ്ധ ടിക ടട്ധട! ഠി 41൦.
My goodness. It looks like you've helped everybody in town.
പുംസ്ഥലിസമ ദ്ധ ല്ലി ടലസ്ധ ഇ ഠിലാഖ്യ്ല ബ്‌.
Yeah, everybody except one.
ര ട്ബ.
- Hey, is it getting dark out? - What? What'd he say?
-൧൯ല്ല്വ ഠി ധന? - യാദ്‌? ൧്യാദ ഠ9 യമ?
Let me say that again. ls it getting dark out?
ദ്ര്ല മവ ധി. ഉനുലില്യാ ഠി?
Now, what was I supposed to do after that?
൧൧൭ ൭1൮ ടലാദ്ധസഭാധമ്‌ ടലില്ാമട ഡ്‌?
They fixed their neon!
[ഗി0ഠ്ല്വാബിത്ഥ സ്ഥ ടബ്‌
- Low and slow? - Oh, yeah, baby!
- ലാ ഠ്ബ്വാലില്മ്ന്‌? ദ, ടന.
Just like in its heyday, right?
ദന നേന നറ ദാബി ത്ഥ?
It's even better than I pictured it. Thank you.
1ലാവാലിറ്ലിവട ലവി. ലന മടി.
Shall we cruise?
ഷുഡ്വന്മ നണമ്ാധ?
Oh, thank you, dear. I'd love to!
ലിനാ ടി, ല്വ ടിയി
- No, no, no. - Lizzie!
മ്മില്‍
l remember when Stanley first asked me to take a drive with him.
൧വ 003 ടട ടഒബിഖ ദ്വ്ല്മിവവാല്ടി-ടില ഠി.
Hey, Miss Sally. May I have this cruise?
ല്‍, വില ഒവഠി നന്മ ബന ടവ?
Of course, Mater.
ലന്ധ ടട്യി॥, 'ഗീമല്‌
..and again and I said, "No." He asked me again, and I said, "No."
൧19 10൭ ടല ൭൮! ദക ലിവ ഠി ൧19 10൭ 1൭൮! ൦ മഡിത്ട യ.
But, oh, he was a persistent little bugger for a two-cylinder.
ല്ലാ ഠി ട്ധിയ നലാടടം
Finally I said, "All right, one little drive."
ചന്ദ ലിവ ടബ്വ്, “ടലഭ്വ്ല്ാ ടല്യ്ദ്‌.
- Hey! - Thanks, Mater.
ലിനാ !൭ട10, 'ഗീ്ല.
Good evenin', you two.
ടല്ലനട നടന, ദഖ്സ്ധാല്ഠ്ധ.
Oh, Stanley, I wish you could see this.
൭൨, ടബിഖ ദ്വിദ്ധിമ്വിത്ധ 001൦0൦൦൦.
- ls that what I think it is? - Oh, I don't know, Flo.
-൧ഠിട്യ്ന്ധ ല്ാ൭ു ല്വന്മട? - ൧4൮ ല്വല്ഡ, ം.
l haven't had a chance to find out. But l am going to find out. Hello.
൧വഡാലഥ്പാണാല്ധ്ു ടിമി ൮1. ല്ല മവ ടിക ല്ഡ നന്‌. 11ല്‍൦.
Not that. That.
ധിയാ. ഖ.
Customers?
ലലാ?
Customers, everybody! And a lot of 'em!
ലലാ ൧൭൦൩ ട്യാഥ നല!
You know what to do. Just like we rehearsed.
ദ്ധ ലിസ ല്വാ നലിഗധ്ധ. ൮4൮) ൯5ലിഖി൨.
It's the ghostlight!
ധന്വാധിലസ്ധ!
We have found McQueen. We have found McQueen!
ഗ്൯ ഠ്ദ്വ്ധന്ാദ്ള്‍ീറ്വേടബ്്‌
McQueen, over here!
[ഗീഠ്ധവ൦ം, ഠ। ടബ്‌!
- Wait, excuse me. - ls it true you've been in rehab?
- നാ, സ്ന നല്‌ - ൧ഠിട്യ്സിത്ധ ഠ। പട ലാണ്ധിനമ്ന്‌?
- Did you have a nervous breakdown? - What?
ദ്ധ ഠി ലിന്ഥ്്വിഗ?
- McQueen's wearing whitewalls! - Your tires balding?
[ഗിഠ്ധ൦൦ ഥന ഷഗി!
Stickers!
ലില്‍! [ഗീഠ്ധടലല്‌!
- Was McQueen your prisoner? - Shoot, no!
- ൧ഠിടിഷ്വ്ഗീഠ്ധലലല്മന്്ിത്ധ? - ഠിില്വ
We're best buds! l ain't braggin' or nothin’,
ദ്ര യ്ബത്ഥി! ധി ന്ധവാല്നടട,
but I was in charge of huntin' him down if he tried to escape.
പവ ഡറുടട ടവ ഥന ഠദ ദ്ധ വലിലാദട.
Sally! Sally!
ടലി
Will you still race for the Piston Cup?
൧ഠിിയ്്വിത്ധ നടി ല്ഖ്ബാല്ധമ്പാദ 20 01ട(ഠ?
- Stickers? - Sally!
- ലിലയ്? - ടലി
Come on, give us some bolt!
1 ബ്ധിറമ്ബ്ഖ്ി ബാടിയ
You're here! Thank the manufacturer! You're alive!
ദ്ധ ഠി ട്ല്‌! തൃധിവഡലവാദഠ്ദ ഹസ്ബ്ധണണ്‍്‌ (ദ്ധ നടി ബി!
- Mack? - You're here! I can't believe it!
്ഗീദല്റ്‌ [ദ്ധ ഠി ടിബി! ചവ മലാണമല്‍!
You are a sight for sore headlights!
ദ്ധ നലന്വാ ടല!
I'm so sorry I lost you, boss. I'll make it up to you!
ഗാ വ ക്വിബ്യമ്ബത്ധ. ൧൮ ടിക ലാധട ടിന്‌
Mack, I, l can't believe you're here.
ചവ മലാല ത്വ ഠി ഠി ട്വ.
Is that the world's fastest racing machine?
൧റ്൭ക൨ ഗല നട (ഗന൧൭ ഒറ. വ്‌ വഥഒ
- ls that Harv? - Yeah. He's in the back.
ധ്‌ - 19. ൧ 09 ഠ ാലല്യ്ഥാ.
- Show us the bolt! - Get back, you oil-thirsty parasites!
ദബഗാധ, ലാട
- Where's the old McQueen? - Actually, this is my good side here.
ബി ടലാലടഡഘ്യല്സ൪ ലാല
- Harv! Harv! - Give us the bolt!
ലബ്‌ പ്ല
- Kid, I'm over here! - How you doin’, buddy?
- ൧൮ ൭09 ഗ്‌ ഥ്‌ - യാ റ്ല്വാല?
My star client disappears off the face of the earth!
ഗഗ (൦൭% ഖഗ 0൭൧.
- How do you think I'm doing? - Lcan explain.
- (൫൧7൭5൭ ഗാദറ്ഒനമ്ഗട (ഭദറ്ദദെ ഒഗ7 -൧ിവ ഠഠില്വ്യലദടിയ്വ.
I'm doing great! You're everywhere! Radio, TV, the papers!
29൧5 7ഗഒ൦ഗ (രഥ വ്‌ സററ! ൧9൨്ഠ, 7, ഗോഗ്‌
You can't buy this kind of publicity! What do you need me for?
കഥ ഒഥഠല ൧ല്‌ ൧൧5 ൧! (രമ്യാ (ഒഥവാല്ഥത്ഥ ഖഗ
That's just a figure of speech, by the way. You signed a contract.
൧൧ ഘര്വാ 5൭൭. ൭൧ ൭9 (൭൧൭
Where are you? I! can't even find you on my GPS.
കഥ ഗ്‌ നട?
I'm in this little town called Radiator Springs.
ദം ഭി ൩ ണന ഒട.
- You know Route 667 It's still here! - Yeah, that's great, kid.
-ര്ര്ധട്ഡ ലിക 69% നാടി! - !4൧ ഒറ്റ.
Playtime is over, pal.
959 ന്ഥ റ്ഒ0 49൭.
While the world's been trying to find you Dinoco has had no one to woo.
ലാലറ(ഒ7ഒ  ഒ്‌ (൭൧, ൧7000 19 ഒറ്ട ടട്ട[ട്യാദ ഗഖ്ലക.
- Who are they gonna woo? - Chick!
- ക്യാ 777 ഒക (ക൭൦7 - ബം
Bingo. In fact, check out what's on the plasma right now.
7ലാദ! ടലര7 ൨൧൭ 'റ്റ 77.
- Show us the thunder! - You want thunder?
- ഗവര്‌ ഥാശ്ഥ്ധ്‌ -കഥഥലഗാശ്‌?
You want thunder? Ka-chicka, ka-chicka!
ക്ഥഥലഗ്ാശ്‌?
- Hey, that's my bit! - You've gotta get to Cali, pronto!
- ല്‍, ദുര ലിവ്‌ - കഥ നടെ ൭ ൧൩൭!
Just get out of Radiation Stinks now, or Dinoco is history, you hear me?
(രല ടട റ്7്‌ ഗേ ൭!9൧ (ഥാ൭ക്റ ടദ്൭ (ദ്യദദ്ഥ ൧൧0ഠ0൧!
Just give me a second here, Harv.
ഥാ ടല, 1.
No, wait, Where are you goin’?
ഒറ (ഒ൧ ഗഖലാലയ?
Get in the trailer, baby. Kid! You want a bigger trailer?
ഗട9ടഥ വന ലല. കഥഥലലലഴ '(ലാഥ ടെ?
Sally, I... l want you to...
ടലി ലിവ ന്ലിലത്വ..
Look, I wish...
ദ്രിദ്ധില..
Thank you. Thanks for everything.
ലന മടി. ലന മടി ഥി ടാലി.
- It was just a road. - No. It was much more than that.
- റ്ധനട്ല്ന ട്വ. - ഠി ലാ ഠ്വ.
Hey, kid! We gotta go. Harv's goin' crazy!
[ഗ്മ നടട॥ ഗയ! ലില്ലി
He's gonna have me fired if I don't get you in the truck right now!
2-11-11: ദ്ധിത്ധ ണടടധിന്തിറി
- Mack, just... hold it for... - You should go.
- [ഗീ ഡാ ടട്ഘ്ലാ -ര്രധവാമ്ഡ്വായി
- 1 know, but... - Good luck in California.
- ലി... - ൭ണഠറട ലാലു ഠി 41
l hope you find what you're looking for.
൧ഡിഘ്വായ്ധ്ധ്പാദ ദ്വ ത്വ വി.
- Sally! - Show us the bolt, McQueen! The bolt!
- ടലി. ടലി... - ്ബ്ധിറമ്നി്യണി നാട ഠി, ്‌ഴിറ്വേടബ്‌
Hey, Lightning, show us the bolt!
10്റിദ്്‌
- Come on, get in the trailer. - Where's the old McQueen?
- ൧൮൧, നടെധ്്ലഒ്‌ - ൧ നന്മ ഗീഡ്ധേണ്‌?
You're a big shining star. You're a superstar.
കഥ ഥഥഥറഴ ഥാലഥട്‌
You don't belong there, anyway.
ലി
Hey, guys! McQueen's leavin’ in the truck!
[ഗിഠ്ധ൦൦ ഠി നല്ലാ!
Hey, are you Doc Hudson?
ദ്ധ ൧൦൦ റ്ധഠ്ടം?
- Yeah. - Thanks for the call.
ലന മടി ക്ഥന്൭ 'ടില്ഠ൦൩.
- You called them? - It's best for everyone, Sally.
- ദ്ധ 1ലില്൦ ന്നറ ഡു റാലി ടണ്ഡം, ടല
Best for everyone or best for you?
1ലാദിധിംടണ്ഡഃ ട്വ റോലിഥിലത്ധ?
I didn't get to say goodbye to him.
൧൮ ലിറ്ല്വാബ്വാല്ധനാ വല്ലോ ടലദണ നു! 0399 913.
Hello, race fans, and welcome to what has become, quite simply,
ലണ്ട്‌ ഠ്ങ്ന്ൃു, 00൭ ലിധ്സാണ ൪..
the biggest event in the history of racing.
ദ്വ ാലന്ഇ ടടല ിന ടല്ല്മ്വ്വാലിധസാമണ.
A three-way battle for the Piston Cup!
ലെലന്വാധ് നാട ഭഘ്ദ 0ഥ്ല്ദ 01500
There's a crowd of nearly 200,000 cars
൧൭9൭ ഠില്ടന 200,000 ഘ്ല്ദ
here at the Los Angeles International Speedway.
ഠി ലം ൧സ്മഘാാട ൦ട ഗ്ലടട ല്‍.
Tickets to this race are hotter than a black leather seat on a hot summer day!
11॥ക്വാല്ധമ്പാദമ്ന ബലാ ടഥിഖ ഠിഠ്ല്ാബ്‌ ലി സ്ഥാ റ്വഠ്ധിധിവിസ്ാദഠ്ദ സ്വട്ന്വാദ്ടട!
The King, Chick Hicks and Lightning McQueen
ഗ്ന, ബടെ ്ബ്ള്‍്ം്ധട..
in a 200 lap, winner-takes-all, tiebreaker race.
ന ഹലിധ്ധാബാലലസ്വ 200 വട ബ്‌.
You know I got a lotta miles on me, but let me tell you somethin’.
൧൮ ഠ്ല്വാണഇന്യണ്ന, ദ്വ ടവ ന്ലധിഖ്ലിത്ഥ..
I never thought I'd see anything like this. This is exciting!
91 ടബ്യ1ിയ വ ലിത്വ 02% ടല്ധ്ധാല്്ബി. വ ണ്ട നലലഡ്യട്ത്ല്‍്‌
In fact, the country has almost shut down
ദ്വിഗ. സ്വസ്ഥ
Hey, King! Good luck in your last race.
ഗ്ന, ടണഠറാലിയ.
- You've sure been an inspiration to me. - Thanks, Junior. Appreciate it.
- ദ്രവ 1510 ട്വാ്ടടി വായി ടവ. - ലിന മടി, പഥം. ചവ നലല.
- Hey, be careful out there, OK? - Yeah, man.
- ബിപി ഠവല ട്ട. - ൭.
Wanna know the forecast? I'll give you the forecast.
പിവല്ഡ ണ്ടിണ്‌? ൧൮ ടിയബാലിത്ബാടഠ്ട ത്വ.
A 100 percent chance of thunder! Ka-chicka! Ka-chicka!
100% ലാല്ധാ ധി്ഥാടെ
Say it with me!
്ലിഖ്ബാല്ടണ്ട മയ്‌
Hey, you! No admittance without a garage pass.
151ലാഠ1ല്‍൨ നടിയാ 035 ററദ്്്വ.
Oh, it's OK. Lightning McQueen knows me!
1510. [ഴിഗ്ധ൦൦ബഭന്മി ലിവ്‌
Hey, Marco, it's a beautiful day for a race, isn't it?
ഗി, ബി 0൮൭ 0ഠല ലാലി ന്ഥ?
- Absolutely, Mr. Andretti. - And good morning to you, Fred.
- ട്വഠിലലന്ധ, ൧൨. ൧൦൭൧. - ൭ലണമ 0, ൦൫൦.
Mario Andretti knows my name! You gotta let me in now!
ഗിം0൦ ൧0൧ ലി്ഡ ന്ന ടവ്‌ ദ്ധ നട്ട്‌ ാലലിത്ന മിവ നടടഥിറ
Sorry, pal.
ഴി, യുഗ.
OK, here we go. Focus. Speed.
ഗ്മ ലിഖ സ്ധിലിത്വ £൦1വട. !(ദില്ധ്ന.
lam speed.
൧൮ ഠിടില്വഭ്ല്യന.
Victory.
(ണ്ടാ.
One winner, two losers.
ദ്ധ ാണല്മ്റു, ദ്ധ യല.
Speed. Speed. Speed. Speed...
(രിച്യന. രില്യ്ധന.
Hey, Lightnin"! You ready?
ധി! ദ്ധ ഠ്ല ടം?
Yeah, yeah, yeah! I'm ready.
൭,൮൭൫ ൧൮ ഠ്ലി ട൦ഠദ!
Mack, thanks for being my pit crew today.
1.൦1: 11: 19ഠ നയ ബിലാ ല്ഡിഘി ബി.
Don't worry about it, kid. It's the least I could do.
൮ ട്വ ാഠില്‍ ടവ ൦1൦0൭.
After all, "Gas Can" is my middle name.
1൭10൧൩ ബ ടല ഭ്വാലത്ധന വ.
- itis? - Not really.
യ? - ഠി.
Nelson! Zoom in. Ready, 16? Take 16.
ദ്നല്മ്ടമിഥിലയ. ലി 16?
And there he is, Lightning McQueen!
[ഠിക്്ഴിറ്വേബ്‌
Missing all week, and then he turns up in the middle of nowhere!
ല॥ബൂ ടല ടന്ബ്ാധ, 'സ്ധഠദണ ്[ധ്വാ! ്50 ൦ നന്മ,
In a little town called Radiator Springs.
ടലാധല ദംഹ്ലാനണടന്ട ടി ഠി.
Wearin' whitewall tires, of all things.
ഴിണമിയി ചല ഗന്ധി ധി.
Hey, where you been? I've been kinda lonely.
ദ്ധി നന്മ [ഴീദ്വേന്‌? ന:
Nobody to hang out with. I mean, except the Dinoco folks.
1:11 11-11-11: 1. ലഭ ൧1000.
And the twins. Of course. The ones that used to be your fans,
ഉ ടി വാ. ്ബാലയ ദ്ധി ലാണ്ന്മ്‌ത്ധ,
but now they're my fans. Listen to what the twins think...
ടലയഷ്ാ ്ട്വ്ടഠി ാ്ന്മ്‌ ടവ.
Shoot!
ചിന
Boogity, boogity, boogity, boys! Let's go racin'!
ഷുധ്നാല്ധ്സാം!
Come on, you can do it!
ദ്ധാാഠില്നില്ഡിത്്‌
Come on, King, make us proud, boy!
ദ്ധ ഥാ, ഗയാ!
Fifty laps down, and The King is still holding a slim lead.
ല്ണടാധിഥ ലവട്നാ്ണ ൦ നടട്നിയ! നട്ന്ംസ്ധ്ധി.
McQueen's got a run on him! He's lookin’ to the inside!
[ഗിഠ്ധലബിഭ ൦00 1601!
Chick slammed the door on him!
ബഗനലബഘാല ന്ധ!
Chick's not making it easy on him today.
ബനസവഡിത്ധിക്നിഭദഠ്ദമ്സു!
Man, he lost so much momentum,
൧19 ഭവി നംണനസ്ധണന
and now he's gonna have to chase him back down!
൭൦൩ ന൯ബട നന്നല്ല ടണ്ഡിദ.
McQueen spins out in the infield!
[ഗിഠ്ധ൦൦0 നസ നടി പ്ല
Just me and the old man, fellas.
സ വ ബില ഡദ്ഖ.
McQueen just doesn't have it today.
ഗിഠ്ധ൦ബല്ഥാണ്ടണമാമ്‌ ലി ല്‍.
- Hey, kid, are you all right? - 1 don't know, Mack.
- [രവ 1951 ല്വാട-ല്വാദ? - £ന്ല്വില,ഗിദം.
I don't think I...
എവ മട ലിവ 19%
I didn't come all this way to see you quit.
ദാ ഠ്ഖ്ദ്ധ 0ധി0മത്ധാധ്പട ഒട.
Doc?
൧൦൦?
Guys, you're here! I can't believe this!
ദ്രസ്ധ ടന്ധദ ഠ്ഖ്!
I knew you needed a crew chief, but I didn't know it was this bad.
എവ ല്ധ്ധിത്ധ ാല്ധിത്ഥ ഭ്ധ നയ. 1ടാനബ്യിയ ടഖ്ല്ഡിം്നി.
You said you'd never come back.
!ദ്ധത്ഠ മ0ലിന്വ സ്വാ! 91.
Well, I really didn't have a choice. Mater didn't get to say goodbye.
൧൮ ലിമ 009൨0. [ഗിമ്ല 151: ടണ്ഡാമ്‌ധാല്വാ ടലമന ലാട.
Goodbye! OK, I'm good.
ലണമ്ന്ന്യാല! ഒറി, മിവ 910 വടട 1.
All right, if you can drive as good as you can fix a road
ദ്വിദ്ധത്ധാഠില്വാദ്്ധ ടലാദിധിത്ധവാലിറവല്ന
then you can win this race with your eyes shut.
!ധ്ധ1ഠ01ല൨ നടമനാ ാലിധസ്ാമമ് ബി ൦ നട്ട സ്വ്ധ്വാ.
Now, get back out there!
ലയ്വാ ദ്ധ ല്‌ ടന!
Hot snot, we are back in business! Guido! Luigi!
ശ് ഠ50ന്ധാ॥! ഡിം! ധി!
You're goin’ up against professional pit crews.
!ദ്ധാട്ടാാ ഠ9ഠ൩1ന൦ഡഗിഘസ്ദലാ! യടി.
- You're gonna have to be fast. - They will not know what bit them!
- [രവ നടട്രി 0൭ന9ട. -[ഗി0ധവലിക്ന ലസ ല്വാട ടില്ാ ന്നറ
Kid, you can beat these guys.
!ദ്ധാാംില്വിയ്ല്വത്ന ന്ന
Find a groove that works for you and get that lap back.
ച ന്മിവയ൭ാലിഭടക, ഠ൩ലാധട ടന്ധിടാധട്ന്മ ൦.
- ls that? - Oh, wow. That's him!
-൧ഠിട്യ്വ്ല..? 111:1
Is that...? That's the Hudson Hornet! The Hudson Hornet's back!
൮ റ്ധഠ്ടംബിി്ംനല്‍! 8൦0, ഗി, 0ഠട൦0 01ം൦നട്‌: ലമാ!
It appears McQueen has got himself a pit crew.
[ഴിഗ്ധ൦൦൦ 1 01ന്‌,
And look who he has for a crew chief!
9൭൦൩ ൦0൦1ടില്ാ ദ്ധ നഴ ഠി!
- Look, man. It's the Hudson Hornet! - Whoa!
- ന്യ പ്ധ റ്ധഠ്ടബിി്ംണല്‍! - [ലീനാ ാദ്ധി!
Well, dip me in axle grease and call me Slick! It surely is.
എിനലം മിഡാല്ജ്ധന്വാട്വ്ധിലി ഠിദ.
Wow, this is history in the making.
4വ്‌ ഒഠ്ഒഒ0 ടലഒഒ.
Nobody has seen the racing legend in over 50 years!
൧60 4ലാറ 20 (ഒറ, 1ഒ൭4ഒ്ഠാദ ലന ഗ൭ന്വാ൭ ഗ്‌൭.
Hey, Doc!
ല്‍ ൧0൦
Come look at this fellow on the radio. He looks just like you.
ഗി ഠി ഠിന ഠം! 8:11: 1001-11-10
Can he catch up to them with only 60 laps to go?
ല്വട്പ്രവച്പ ല്ലി
You're goin' great, kid. Just keep your head on.
ദ്ധ ഘാദ്‌. !ദ്യിഖ്ബ്ര്ടന്ടി.
Hey, shrimpie, where did McQueen find you, huh?
൧ ന്ന ഗീഠറ്ധംപ്വന്ഥാ്ധ?
Those round things are called tires, and they go under the car!
8ല്മാധിദ സ ഖ ൭൩ ന്ഥ്സട ഠി ൧ധ്ല്വിഭഘ്ല്‍!
No! No, no! You'll have your chance. You will have your chance.
ദ്ധ ടിക 90 ഹല്ലാ ന്ധ, ഡിം! ദ്ധ ടിക 90 ഹല്ധണാ യവ.
Oh, kid's just tryin’ to be a hero, huh?
൧19 ലോദ ന്ലലുദഠി യത?
Well, what do you think of this?
൧൧൭ ലാലാഠ്ല്ാദ ത്വ ന്മ?
Yeah, that's it, kid.
ര, നണട മാട
What?
൧൧൭!
Whoa! Git-R-done!
1ടിയിത്ന ല്വാവയലാല്ധ!
I taught him that. Ka-chow!
പ 1:11:121:1,
What a move by McQueen! He's caught up to the leaders.
ദരിയ ലാമ ൦൦൩ [ഗിറ്വേടബ്‌ ൧19 9511 0: നാല ന്ന! ലോ.
Yeah. This is what it's all about.
ബി്വിവഘ്ലാട്ട്സുഒ.
A three-way battle for the lead, with ten to go!
ലെലന്വാധ്ന്റാട 031 ൦ 10 ല്വട്നാ്ബിാ!!
Look at that boy go out there!
ലിനാധാഠ്ട്റ്ധാണ്യി!
No, you don't.
1ഠിപ്ല്വാഠിലി
Doe, I'm flat! I'm flat!
൧൦൦, ഒ ടവ ഥല്‌
- Can you get back to the pits? - Yeah, yeah. I think so.
- 8ംില്വിത്ധ!ഭ ണി? - ൭, ഖഡ്ധഒട6ദധാവ്‌ലി.
Hey, got a yellow. Bring it in. Don't tear yourself up, kid.
ഉല്ല ഡാ. 1൭5൧൦ പ൭൩ ഈടലിറിക്ഥ ക.
We gotta get him back out there fast
[ഗ്മ നടട॥ ശ്ധധത്ഥ ഠി ടന്ധിഃ ടലലാട്‌ സ്ധഘന്ന
or we're gonna be a lap down, and we'll never win this race!
ട്്ധന്മ 0ല്ക് നടന്മഥാ!
Guido! It's time.
ദി! ല്ലാം നട.
Hey, tiny, you gonna clean his windshield?
ദ്ധ നലിഗട്ട്വിത്ഥ ഗ്ന ഠി?
I don't believe it!
ചവ മിലാ.
That was the fastest pit stop I've ever seen!
ധിഘസ്ദ്ലാ! 09100 ്മട ല്വവാല്മ്വിന്മ്‌
It was a great stop, but he's still gotta beat that pace car out!
൧19 ന്മ 00൧0 ഖല റസ്ദ൦.
It's gonna be close.
ധാധ്ന്മന്ഥ.
He's back in the race!
൧൭ റ്൭൨ (കന്ഥഒ്7്‌ ൭ ാല്ധ്്ഥദ!
- Guido, you did it! - Way to go, Guido!
ദലം, ത്വ ലു!
This is it. We're heading into the final lap and McQueen
[ഗമ 1൪ വട[ന്ൃദ്ബം്ച്സ്പ്റിറ്വേണ
is right behind the leaders. What a comeback!
റല്മഠിടാദ്ധി ഠിരാലല്യ്ാ ഭ്ധു. ലല്ന്യിയ്മസുരു ഘാ
A hundred and ninety-nine laps, and, baby, it all comes down to this!
199 വടമ ്൦ബില്ലാലല്ഡമ്സുത!
This is it, kiddo.
ബില നടു.
You've got four turns left. One at a time.
1൪ സ്ഥ ടല്‍ല൪ 31. ദ്ധ ഠ്‌ ടബ്൨.
Drive it in deep and hope it sticks.
്ധ ഭ ലി ൩ 0ലല്വാഭര! ഠി മട ദ.
McQueen's going inside!
[ഗിഠ്ധ൦ബിഭ ദി ല്ല
- Chick and The King are loose! - [think McQueen's out!
- ബ്ബ ഗ്നാ വിണു ടിനി -[ഗീഠ്ധട 'ലിഭ്ല ഠിദ്ധി ഹാല്ധമ്പാദമ്ബ്‌
- McQueen saved it! - He's back on the track!
- ൧9 ടല്ണമിയസ്സു! - ൧9 ന്ധ! മട ദ
- Float like a Cadillac... - Sting like a Beemer!
- ലഘ്വാധ് ന 309൦... [ഗീ നാണ 8ണല്‌!
Lightning McQueen is gonna win the Piston Cup!
[ഗിഠ്ധ൦൦ ലിഖ നന്മ ല്ലി ലട
Come on! You got it! You got it, Stickers!
!ദ്ധാലിഖയ, ൧ലിലല്‍യ്‌!
lam not comin’ in behind you again, old man.
ഠി ലട ത്വ, ഇഡ!
Yeah!
1 1)
I won, baby! Yeah! Oh, yeah!
ചവ നന്മ്ന്യ, ടാ!
What's he up to, Doc?
൧൧൭ ഠി, ൧൦൦
What are you doin’, kid?
൧൧൭ ദ്ധാാധ?
I think The King should finish his last race.
എവ ടാ ഗ്നു ണ്ഡ ്വടിഖ്്ാല്ധമ്പാദന ഘി.
You just gave up the Piston Cup, you know that?
!ദ്ധിരനബിക്ണ ലം[ദ ൧൭൦൩.
This grumpy old racecar I know once told me somethin’.
൧൧൭ ഭലാ ഡാല്ബ്ധട ലിട്ഡ മിവ ടട്ധമ്ബ.
It's just an empty cup.
9 ബന ദ്യ !രടംു.
Darrell, is pushing on the last lap legal?
ഉല, ഠ്യ നല! ഠി ്വട്നാലലമ്പ ഖ്ാന്ലിത്ന?
He's not really pushin’ him.
൧1 ധി 101൮൦
He's just givin’ him a little bump draft.
റ്ധണ നലവാദട്ധിത്ടില്ധ ട൦॥൨.
Hey. What? What's goin' on?
൧൧൭൦ ചാ ൮൬ ലാലിദവ?
That's what I call racin' right there.
ധില്സഭ ല്വവാബാഠ॥ ഗല്ധ്സാണ.
- Don't embarrass me, Fillmore. - That's my hot rod.
- ൭൩ ന്ല്ധിത്ന ലവ, ലി॥നഠ്ട. [ധി ടലി വ.
Come on, baby, bring it out! Bring out the Piston Cup!
ധാ ഠി ഭവ, ടമ! മാധവ ലല ല്ട്രല്‍്‌
Yeah! Now, that's what I'm talkin’ about!
ധില്സഭ ല്വിയ്ലത്ല്‍്‌
Hey, how come the only one celebrating is me, huh?
(രന്ല്വാ സ൭ ടവ നയിത്ന്‌!
Where are the girls? Bring on the confetti!
൧ നന്മ റ്റടഠിടാറുഠിട? മാധ ഭ്ധലരസ്ലി!
Easy with the confetti. What's goin’ on?
50-05 ഠബബ്രബ്ലി വ.
Come on, snap some pictures. I gotta go sign my deal with Dinoco!
1്റിയ്വാഠുമ്സാല. ചവ ന്യുന ഗലി 900 ഥന!
What's wrong with everybody? Where's the happiness?
(രന്ല്വാട ൭൦ ടസ്ഡം ഈ?
Hey! This is the start of the Chick era!
ബിദ്വാണ്ധ്ദ്ന ഒ ബെ
- Thanks, Lightnin’. - You're welcome.
- ലിന മടി. - ഭണട-ടടനമ.
- Way to go, King! - You're still the car!
- ളമറ്റട, ൩൬൮. - ദ്രവ നടി ലാണ്‌
You're The King! Yeah!
ദ്ധ ഠിടില്വഗ്!
- You made us proud, kid! - Congrats on the loss, me bucko!
-ര്രധവാധദ്ധികിലാബാഠ! - ചന്ന മ്ടടഭ്ഖി്ന്ബ്‌
You got a lotta stuff, kid.
ദ്ധ ണദ്ധ്ട്നണ്!
Thanks, Doc.
ലിനാ !൭ട॥, 0൦0൦.
How ‘bout comin’ over here and talk to me a minute?
ഗിം01ഭ ട്വ ല്ട്ബാ്യ 9900 ലവ ടലഭ്യ്യാ.
Son, that was some real racin' out there.
ധവാലിധസ്ാമര ലാ.
How'd you like to become the new face of Dinoco?
൧൧൭ ൭9 ദ്ധ യ ൧0൦00൮൬൭ 0?
But I didn't win.
ല്ല മവ ലിന.
Lightnin’, there's a whole lot more to racin' than just winnin’.
ലലിധസ്പാന ധിത്വ ടല്യഠ്ച ധനനയ.
He was so rusty, when he drove down the street
൧ മനട്ലാലിയ്ല്‌,
buzzards used to circle the car!
സനാ ഘു ടട്ല്ധിഭബസ്ഥന ഠി!
Thank you, Mr. Tex, but...
ലിനാ ൭51, 6൨. 79൦.
..but these Rust-eze guys over there gave me my big break.
ദ്വ ഒരിത്‌ ്വട്ലം ലി വ ല്ലാ ന്ന.
I'm gonna stick with them.
ചവ ടിത്ിര്ഷി ട്ടാ ന്നി
Well, l sure can respect that.
എവ ഹന്നമ്‌ഭ്ധധധടബിത്ഖ.
Still, you know,
ദ്രിദ്ധ ഠി ല്വാദ-ഖ്വാമ ൮൮ 1001ല്‍ മിവവാടന്ധ, ഥ്ല്ഡ ട്വ.
I sure appreciate that. Thank you.
൧വമസട. "ന്൭ടി.
Actually, there is one thing.
ലാലല, മഠദ ടദ്ധ വാലിയ.
Hey, look at me! I'm flyin’, by golly!
വാദ ലവ! ഷവ ബണ്!
I'm happier than a tornado in a trailer park!
ചവ ടാ ഠാ!
I think it's about-a time we redecorate.
എവ മട ൭൩ ധാ നട ന്മ ബ്ദട ടബ്ഡിദ.
Hi. Lightning McQueen told me this was the best place in the world
[ഗിഠ്ധ൦ബിത്ദ ബി 1ന്വാമ 0100 31
to get tires.
10ഗ്ലാിത്ന ഖ്‌
How ‘bout setting me and my friends up with three or four sets each?
൧൮ ഠ്ബബിയധണിയ്മന നവാ ൯9 മ്ട്ധ സ്ഡ൭ ടല. ടട.
Guido! There is a real Michael Schumacher Ferrari in my store.
ദധി! ൧൭ ന്ഥ ഗിന്ടല്‍ ടഗ്ഡണ്ടണലെ ബ്ബ! റിനഭഠ് മയി
A real Ferrari!
ജ്‌]!
Punch me, Guido. Punch me in the face.
ധമ്പാധിലി്വ. സമ്ബാധില്വ ഠ। സ്ധ൭.
This is the most glorious day of my life.
ബബ ന്മഥവ൭ ലാന 0 ഠി വഠ്ധാ ലവ.
Just passin’ through?
ഭല്വ്മില്ധ?
Actually, I thought I'd stop and stay awhile.
1ല്പാദിത്ന ന1ധാി ട്ബ ടട്ഷ്ല്വാ.
- [hear this place is back on the map. - itis?
൧൮ ഠബുല ന്ദ്‌ ബി 50 ലഭ! ടന്ധിട
is setting up his big racing headquarters here.
വാഡിയ ാഥ്വാല്ലാദ്‌ ഠി ടി.
Really? Well, there goes the town.
ദൂത? ല്ച്ധിടില്വാ്ല ല്‍.
You know, I really missed you, Sally.
എവ നദ ന്നാധിത്ലത്ധ, ടല.
Well, I create feelings in others they themselves don't understand and,
൧വ ഘ്ധടിഖ്ബാല്ടടാണ ഠിന ൦൬ ഴു സട ടിവ്ല്മ്ണ ൦,
blah, blah, blah.
ദൃതില്ഡ.
McQueen and Sally parked beneath the tree,
0ഗഥേധടണെ റ്റെ ൭9 ഗാലഭറ്ട ൧൭൧൭0 ൧07൭..
K-i-s-s-.., i-n-t!
..5ഒറ്ററ ൧ലഗഥ്വാഥ്ഥ
Great timing, Mater!
ഗീടാ ദ്ധ നന ടടട്ധി, രില്‌
He's my best friend. What're you gonna do?
൧1 ൭ധബത്ലാ ലിവ. ൧൧൭ 0ഠല്വാധദ്റ്‌
So, Stickers, last one to Flo's buys?
ബാ ജന്നി ഠി ഭഠ്ല 0൦ ഭന്മാലദു്‌?
I don't know. Why don't we just take a drive?
5സ്ല്വം. ഘാ ൭൭൭ ഗ0ഠ്ധവാലിദ്്നില്മ്ന ടയ?
Nah.
ലന.
Yeah! Ka-chow!
ലാട!
All right, everybody please keep together now.
ലന്ധദ്റ്ബ്പാണാഠാലി
We is now entering the Doc Hudson wing of the museum.
ഗ്രഗല്പച്പഠഷ്പ ലേ ൧ചഥച്ി 1 ഗ്ര 27 വലച്ച ഷ്പ 1952
Wow. Unbelievable. That many wins in a single season.
ടിയ ഠ0ലമഖ. ലോസുദ്്ലവ്ധ !ഭണലന്മന്യ്ന ന ടദ്ധ സ്വട്ന.
He's the real deal, Junior. The Hudson Hornet was my inspiration.
ഉദ്ധ ഡി. ്ധഠ്ടംബിംനല്‍ ഠിടില സാല നട്ടി ടവ.
Excuse me, son. Is Doc Hudson here today?
൧൦൦ റ്ധഠ്ട൦ന ൭ ഠി ട്ബിഘി ബ്‌?
Sorry, Mrs. The King, I think Doc went out for a drive or somethin’.
ഗാ, ൧൨. ൩൭. ദേര ടാ ഠി ദ്ധല ധാല്ടിട്ല.
Well, you sure ain't no dirt boy.
ദ്ധ നണട ടാലി ടിന ാലിധന്വാധ
Not today, old man. I know all your tricks.
ലി ബിദ്ധല്വാംട്വഖ്ച്ല്വത്ഥ ല്ധ, ഗു ഡാ. ചവ ല്ഡ ടണ്ഡടഘ്ദ്വിത്ഖ.
Doc! Doc!
൧൦൦! ൧൦൦
Not all my tricks, rookie!
ധി ടന്ധട, ഹല്ധമ്പാദ ബ്‌!
Attention! Kiss the pavement goodbye.
ഗ്ഗ ലച ടട
When I'm finished, you'll have mud in places you didn't know you had!
പ്ൂം൩ ലി്വ ദ്ദ ധന്വാധ ഠി ന്വാബ്വ ന്ധ 151: ടാാ1ര ൧൧.
- Yo, I've never been off-road! - Well, that's gonna change right now!
1 ഠിഖബാബ്ധാല്വ്‌
About face! Drop and give me 20 miles!
പദ്ധ്വിഖ്ബാദഠ്ക ഠ്കഠലി ടവ 20 ബ്ബ!
Go! Go! Go, go, go, go, go! Go!
ഷുഡ്‌ കൃഡ്ബ്‌
Man, now I got dirt in my rims!
൧൧൭ ൧്വാധ ഠി ന്ന യ്‌
It's my hood! It's my hood!
ധഡാഠ ലിഡ്‌ ബ്‌ ലിയ
l ain't seen this thing in 20 years!
ഉ 20 ന ടവ ഗാന്ധ ബ്‌!
Well, it fits perfectly. How do I look?
ട്ടാ. 'ഗീടണമന3 ഡ്വാദ ലിവ?
Oh, dang.
എനി
You are a toy car!
കഥ ക്ര നദഗമ്ഥ!
You are a sad, strange little wagon and you have my pity. Farewell.
൫൧ ഒററ (ഭഥ്‌)൭ നല൮വ്വെര്ഥ റ്ദറ ഒധ 54൩0൭ റ്റു (൪൧.
Oh, yeah? Well, good riddance, you loony!
290൧5 (൭൧ റ 790൭9, ൮൧൭൪
Hey, I hate to break up the road rally, guys, but they're here!
൧്ഥര്ഥ ഖധ റ൭ ഗെറ്റ്‌ ഛ൭ഥട്ഥ ൨
Birthday guests at three o'clock!
7ല്ഖനഥ ഗ്ഗ, ഹാഥഡ്‌ 0൭!
Oh, man! Whoever does the voice of that piggy truck,
ടില്വാ വയ ധ്‌ ധമ്മ തല്ല.
I'm tellin’ ya, he's one great actor!
ടല വലുതാ ഘാദ്‌.
We're banished, genius! Stuck here in this wasteland without chains!
ഫ്ലിപ്‌ സ്ഥ്ധഗിധ്ന്മെ
But, Mike, the Boomobile's in trouble! She needs our help!
7ഒ0! 20൧0൧9 വന നഒ6ഒ97
You're still not listening!
കഥ നട 4൭വലഴെറ്റെറട.
Welcome to the Himalayas! Snow cone?
ക്ല! റട[ഒഥറ്റ (ര ഥ്നലഖൃക! ൭൨0. ഗഗ?
Oh, that Abominable Snowplow is quite the comic thespian!
ഴി ടാ ചല നല്ധധിത്ല്‍്‌
Just get in there. Go! Go, go, go!
ധ്്ലഥഷ്പ (൧൧൧൫൧9൨൦
Circus cars?
ഗരഭ്ര ട്ര?
How can you be circus cars?
ടന (൭൧ ൧0൦ഒ൨്‌ (കട ടദ്ഥ്രട?
These are the lousiest circus cars in the world,
ഗ07വകലട ഗ്കട ലം.
and they're gonna make me rich!
ററ ൩൦% ലര്ഥഒസെര്ഥ ഒധ ൭൭
Wait a minute here.
[ഴില്ല്യ ൩൭ റുധന്ലിത്ഥ ഥലടഡ്൩ ലിനാ ൭.
What kind of a cut-rate production is this?
ബി നാറിയ ന്ധ ലാമ?
Oh, for the love of Chrysler, can we please ask someone for directions?
8ഠില ലിവ ടട്ല്വാദ ഡ്ബ്ധിധ്യ്ന?
No! There's an on-ramp close! I know it! I can feel it!
19010 ൧09 ലബുബാല്ല്‍യ്ന. എവ ല്‌! ചവ ലാ ടലി!